e e
[Music]
try
to but I can't hear a word you
say talking loud not saying
much
[Music]
but but I get
I'm going to Pro nothing to
lose away far away bre the sh you take
your rain far
away
away down but I fall I am
TI you sh me down but I fall I am TI
[Music]
[Applause]
I
down but it's you who have further to
fall go
down on to
[Music]
love Raise Your
Voice sticks and stones break my
bones talking loud
saying
much
I'm nothing to lose far away far away
break the sh you take
your far away far
away down but
I'm I am
TI show me down but I won fall I am
[Applause]
[Music]
wow what's up y'all
morning morning
morning listen every
day is a good morning every day you want
to know
why because you can't put an alarm clock
in the
graveyard and they wake
up so for some of y'all lazy ones that
got to set the alarm to wake yourself up
and your body hasn't set it for you as
of yet
it's a beautiful thing to wake up every
day so uh let me see somebody said the
mic is low let see is that better how's
that is either that or or it got to be
your Walmart TV whichever
one is my voice echoing
you know they come in and submit the
Burger
King Burger King
menu they're like we want in so loud
that we can hear your stomach
Grumble
okay cool no Echoes great great so you
got you got to return that TV brother
the Walmart they got you you got to
return that
TV so
um actually I want to do a top down
analysis with y'all real quick uh let me
go
to um the current contract
right let me just do this
first I should probably give youall
levels to set until like next week right
so we all like yeah do it do it
uh
so do you guys see that
we cook that low right
there when I did a top down analysis
with the group yesterday I told them
that I was
anticipating um after this low was taken
I was anticipating this low uh to be
taken out as well this is that uh
Wednesday January 31st low um and
overnight y'all that yall y'all saw that
momentum overnight that was that was
something 360 points down
overnight that was amazing that's why I
said that with with these higher time
frame
moves this is it's not your business as
a day
trader this is not your
business trying to figure out if this
log is taken so does that mean that now
we go back up into no that's not your
business when these higher time frame
lows get taken they take them with Force
yes they they split right through them
like a banana take them with Force what
is your business is after these
people are ran
out you have enough money at that point
to be able to buy back up or trade back
in
so the other day we um did the top down
we talked
about the sng responsible for the break
right so we get that out the
way when we go down hit the top of it
this you know we always anticipate
something like that uh off of this move
even if this is not set to whole there
still is a possibility that price trades
lower y'all y'all see every weekend how
we get all of this news that just throws
us down the other way again so um you
know you don't want to be too much in
haste um you know to have an opinion
that oh now we hit here yeah we're going
to get back up into the previous range
there although it is a possibility I
mean you look we have this High we have
this low right we close below so that
validate dat at the high right we closed
above so that caused the low to be a
protected low This Is Us taking out that
protected low that's what this move is
so when
we bring up the previous range that we
had right
there we know
that the thing we have is this
fractal so the highest point we
anticipate price to get to that's if it
pushes to this fractal is at least right
into the center of the fractal 50% of
the fractal with the possibility of just
flushing up above the fractal and then
taking us back down like that back below
it so when we go back below it that
could give us enough momentum below here
to move us back up above the high that
was put in there to actually trade back
into the previous range trade back into
the 50% of the move so um last
year um well I think it was early this
year I had mentioned that this is
probably just going to end up being in a
Range so what we have here is the bottom
of the range and what we have here is
the top of the
range and this is essentially
the environment that we're going to be
in we accumulate right after taking out
what well we we don't have the data on
this one but after taking out an all
high to the left we accumulate so we
took out that alltime high from 2021 so
we
accumulate and when we
accumulate that creates enough orders
enough momentum for us to either expand
higher or trade lower so we need to
understand that when we get into the
environment that we're accumulating in
we need to trade with an accumulating
mindset I say that in all the videos
that I post on this channel I say that
you know in the mentorship as well um
you know talk about it on Twitter
everywhere you need to trade in an
accumulating mindset somebody asked me
what they what I thought Bitcoin was
doing let's go to bitcoin I had
mentioned that we traded up above this
old high right on the day daily right
the previous all-time high as well
2021 what do we have going on
here the same thing we were expecting on
NQ we have accumulation taking place so
this is the bottom of the range right
and this is the top of the range right
so you prioritize shorts in the top of
the range you prioritize Longs in the
bottom of the range and that's literally
the whole essence of range Trading
so for us to be in a larger range around
here on on uh
um uh uh whatever this pair's name is
enq for us being a larger
range on enq is the same exact
thing we trade from the bottom of the
range to the top of the range to the
bottom of the range to the top of the
range until price does what until it
begins to trade lower and Target lows
right heads back to the origin right or
we end up going back for highs again now
how would we you know essentially Point
those things out um that's let me go
back to the other contract
that's that is BAS based
on what we do within this range
so if you look
at the tops of the range let me just
just take this
there if you look at the tops of the
range you see that anytime we trade it
below and close below we trade it back
to the bottom of the range right same
thing here in the bottom of the range we
trade up close above we head back back
to the top of the range we close above
right we continue to head up
right this provided a close below but
then we flush back up above the high
that's that's fine th those things you
know they occur um and that's why you
got to make sure you take your profit so
we end up getting a mini range within
here but then when we trade back up
again first of all the the closure above
put us back into the top of the range
the closure below put us back into the
bottom of the range and at no point no
point as as we began coming down did we
get a closure back up above to price
higher so we continue to get closures
below right closures below right so in
the event that and this is not just even
you know counting today today could just
you know end in a Range end as a dogee
or something like that remember we
anticipate that it's getting back to
this fractal but in the event
that we
get a closure above let's say this
candle closed like this it's not
currently closed so you don't want to
utilize this you know while it's still
alive in the event that we get a body
closure above like
that then we know
that that's a possibility ility to put
us what we mention up
above this
high so us trading back up above this
High we would nine times out of 10 get a
rejection out of here back into that
previous range below should we end up
closing below a bullish candle so we end
up closing with a body below bullish
candle now that gives us that momentum
to come back down and attack these
lows so it's essentially following the
same thing within the range whether it's
the lows of the range whether it's the
highs of the range it's the same exact
thing so being that we're in a Range a
range has structure on a lower time
frame but the range
itself the range itself is not bound by
structure it's bound by
extremes that's where we talk about the
bottom of the range and the top of the
range so you'll see structure created
and broken so many times within the
range
right many times within the range you
see structure created and
broken but on a lower time frame you'd
see structure leading to those different
areas the the last thing you want to
do is in the center of the Ring
range you're holding a position
here saying that price is going lower
and we end up trading higher or saying
that price is going higher and we end up
trading
lower this the thing you don't want to
do what would you what we understand
with this is that the previous range
that we have according to structure with
that body closure that we just got
is
here right so we know
that the run into this would just be
providing a rejection back down now
could we reject down trade back in again
off of something in here fail there
create an equal high within here to drop
down and now take the lows absolutely
but that would just end up creating
what that would just end
up sorry bringing us down here for what
another move up
again and we' just end up walking
structure down on a higher time frame
right and it doesn't mean that if we
push up above that inside High there we
can push up above there and not close
we get no closure there we trade back
below again look at what this leads into
this this kind of price
action this kind of price action ends up
leading into what later on in the
year if that's the way price began to
move because from this high right here
when we first got here this is
December so from
December into where we currently are in
April we've been in the same
spot yeah slightly higher
than you know where where uh uh the end
of December had us but it's still the
same
area so we need to understand that
instead of trying to pick tops and
bottoms based on the higher time frame
we need to trade with that that
ranged mind
understanding that we're in
accumulation anytime we trade below old
low anytime we trade above old high we
get
accumulation
so that's just it for the higher time
frame
context
um for me
here all I had marked out within here
was this
fractal you guys first saw me
come on actually no I I had removed it
before I came on this fractal that's
below
here so in the event that
price trades below this low sorry not
that
one trades below this low and
consequently below this low
too this is where you end up having a
move back into the previous range so
there's uh 39 minutes left on that let
me actually just look at what else we
got
here
um yeah this is this is
fine go to
15 yeah this is
fine f Bal they was trading back up and
then putting a body below this uh low
right here
431 should end up looking for these
lows and tapping back into this
um 4our fractal
below so yeah that that's why you guys
saw me with this this drawing in here
first you saw the trend line Traders
killing everybody they they be cooking
they got their own system and and they
be cooking y'all because y'all want to
trade every detail in the
market so yeah that that's
essentially um what I have there's a
possibility of another bounce
406 uh but ultimately I want to see us
get below that uh
387 so I figured out I'll go through
that
um top down with y'all um just so you
understand
that we are not in the the environment
to be picking bottoms and tops I see
people talk about
um stocks will never go up in their
lifetime again you know you got all
these macroeconomic people you know who
are like we were right it's
coming it's on the
way it's coming you know like they
they've been waiting for this crash for
for a very long time they call it a melt
up a melt up now now we just creating
names to try to avoid being wrong the
market was supposed to crash but it's
melting up now what it's bullish that's
what you mean you were wrong you were
wrong it's bullish like just let's
let's let's say when we wrong okay we
wrong we wrong you know and when we
right
we glorious feeling when we're right but
when we're wrong we need to admit that
we're wrong it's not a melt up caught
you by surprise you would try to call
the top and you try to call the top and
the top and then the top again and then
the top again and then the top again and
everybody just eating up all your
prophets on the way up you you were
wrong and then when I started hearing
influences you know like in other spaces
um Fitness influences and you know
people who who um do podcast and stuff
like that when I started hearing him
talk about these things it's like oh
yeah oh no this
is you know you get Andrew Tate talking
about a melt up and I'm just like
[Music]
oh oh you know they they just
they that's that's
just not wanting to say that you were
wrong right you can stay wrong for that
long come
on strong and wrong making up different
words to the trying is melting up okay
yeah got you hey my man my man Sam was
in the building what's up baby
profitable losers in the building y'all
that man
if I had your hands i' cut mine off
that's that's that's an amazing brother
right there doing some amazing things uh
in the community uh happy to have you
here
brother uh so you know with with that uh
uh topown that we we just gave consider
that over the next few
weeks consider it over the next few
weeks right consider it over the next
few weeks
and trade based on that stop holding
positions that come back to
you stop holding positions that you
wanted to go further you wanted to run
more and then it took everything it gave
you from
you stop doing
that okay it's it's very important this
Market is not made for
us anybody that's on this live stream I
promise you none of us have enough money
to pick tops and bottoms in this market
this Market hasn't been it's not made
for
us so if we can come in and take money
out of thin air if we can come in and
take money from somebody on the other
side that's losing because their lack of
self-discipline you know the the way the
world works is those who manage risk
take from those who
don't so the same people in this market
all trading together
remember everybody talking about getting
payouts and all that other stuff
somebody lost their fees for you to get
that
payout somebody didn't exercise they
risk on that somebody paid 50 $60,000 in
payouts I mean in in fees in two three
months in order for you to walk away
with with that payout on the other
side so those who manage risk take from
those who do not
and the sooner you understand that
you'll see that you what what needs to
be in your rules of Risk
Management what needs to be in your
rules of Risk Management right is paying
yourself everybody has all these
different rules of how to Trail a runner
and how to do all of this but what about
the rules of paying yourself when is it
enough right you can make money on a
move that you thought it was going
further than that and you were wrong
about that but you still made money with
it you still made
money you still able to protect your
Capital so it's
um you know important for y'all to
uh add that to a part of of risk
management pay yourself or as my man
prop say let them pay you to get
out and it's gonna hit every time let
them pay you to get
out no reason that you stubborn
believing that it got to hit your TP or
come all the way back to your stop
loss I watched some one guy I see these
charts on Twitter all the time there was
this one guy he you know had a position
you know like that on on Euro USD he was
aiming for 4 R you know some something
like
that he's aiming for hold I'm trying to
there we go he's aiming for four
I watch price get all the way up
here
right and see it come all the way back
down
here and his post
was
negative 1
R1 R I'm sorry that that went almost
three
are and within your risk management
approach because you weren't right about
that this small little thing within this
you allow yourself to give back all the
profits and then go right back to your
stop
loss that that's the tax the the tax
they pay they talking
about that's that's not you didn't pay
any
tax you got to write off from your
foolishness
so in your in your your you know risk
management
approach just be sure that you guys are
including
that pay yourself lock something
in this whole thing
everything that we do
here it's about paying
yourself nothing else but paying
yourself we don't come here to sing
Kumbaya we don't come here to laugh and
and and joke and and you know just waste
away with our
time and not monetize it you shouldn't
be on social media if you're not making
money and trading what are you doing
arguing with Joe Biden he even read
those
tweets what are you
doing
yo it's just some crazy stuff you know
so I want y'all to to get a little
better with with um those
techniques want you to get a little
better with that let me look at what's
on the the five second in there no they
they still they still taking this down
y'all
yeah they still taking this down there's
a little bounce out of
this 5sec down candle but they still
taking this down look at this like this
this is this is how want you guys to
frame
it so this is going down like
this like that
right what you need
is a manipulation down
down up looks like they about to run it
we'll see if they take out this High
then more than likely they're going to
go back to this
here uh let me see there right
there but they're running this down in a
channel more than likely you get the
manipulation below and price comes back
up to take out these highs within it
right so the only thing you want to keep
is this up
above when it makes that run back in the
only thing that's worth shorting from is
this up above not any of these highs
within here that's for anybody to trade
down on a second time
frame so
like I said we're going to hit this when
the when the down
candle trades into this
Zone here when it trades into this
depending on how far it
goes that's where a nice little buy stop
to trade back into the
range comes from so Trail these down
candle highs until you get in into this
Zone and then you buy stop
it and we watch price trade back up to
take out some of these highs in here why
because some of these highs in here are
not a part of one minute
structure and this is that that uh
uh there's a 4H hour imbalance here as
well as a 4-Hour fractal
just moving this out the
way oh
SO trading is easy we
just make it difficult uh weekly close
do for OB think I do not speak the
language at
all I don't I don't know what you would
you um
do we have an interpreter here hold let
me see if I can find
one do we get do we got an interpreter
y'all we got we need somebody to speak
cby I going to try
[Music]
to
yeah we get CBA in
here do
weekly close
4 h
o yeah
I you you gonna have to you got to wait
till somebody in the
chat
uh in chat helps me out with that one
because
I I want to serve you the best that I
can you know but there's a language
barrier there
it's going to be difficult so so look
guys
look we have that lower time we're
talking about lower time frame swings
right we have that one there we have
another one there we have another one
there we have another one there we have
another one there so we have
these lower time frame
Swings with
these higher time
frame lows and highs right there right
another low here putting another high
right trade below it give us a body so
we're looking for another higher time
frame uh um
pullback as a third um high in order so
what still bring us back
below so we're still
anticipating that pric is looking to
trade lower than where we currently are
we just don't want to be shorting at the
time that price is pulling
back we want to make sure that we're you
know staying on the side of when price
is going to do what there there's people
there people that what they do is they
go short here and price pulls up 84
points on them they go short here and
price pulls up 84 points on them or 80
points on them so you just want to make
sure that you're not
um shorting at certain lows that prices
getting ready to pull back you know
within
that so that's why I have us now we the
50% of the uh the fractal
there we more than likely
uh I'm thinking we deliver a one to one
on it
but we'll just
wait oh you supposed to be vortexing
right now
Hi D when is the back next back to
membership I don't I don't I'm not sure
I don't know I'm not
sure
um the the one that I'm working on now
it's a tougher group
um you know I'm trying to make sure that
they uh
uh you know sort of get what they need
to so when the next group comes in there
are other people there that's able to um
give them them a
hand on uh uh you know what's needed I
mean you got to think about it I'm one
person like you even look at Sam's group
you know profitable losers group I'm
more than sure that you know as many
people as in his group he's not able to
really answer the question that everyone
has not able to serve everybody not able
to you know do certain things you know
that that he wants to with every single
individual because it's just a lot of
people and it's one person you know um
Dave are you still looking for people to
hire yes yes I am um yes I'm going to
put that application out
soon yes
uh there's people in the class who lie
about watching the free playlist I mean
I I think that's everywhere you know
like I remember one guy um coming to me
and telling me that profitable loser
strategy doesn't work and I was like
well did you back test it and he goes
well that's just
icts and dog like first of all
we don't allow pets in here there's no
pet
policy so the the end
dog the the you know the hogw whatever
all all the animals you want to talk
about we we don't allow that in here but
what you have to do is that you have
to back test no matter what it is that
somebody tells you you have to back test
it
period you have to back test it know if
ands or butt you have to back test it
it's not possible to you know be able to
get any of this knowledge that we have
transferred to you so you could apply in
the proper context if you have not back
tested it there's no
way so you got to make sure that you
back test period
no matter who you're learning from
you're never going to learn one thing
that's going to be the holy grail for
you so let me move this
here
um that Spike up that I'm looking for at
least is going to go above
this uh 407
there so what you want to see is
just that first candle that closes up
above and leaves that
imbalance behind like
that yeah leaves that imbalance behind
so we're at what is it we hit 10:30 yet
nope 10:30 is the next
candle so you want to see a bullish
candle
run take out a previous candle's High
close
but then you want to see some
imbalances um start to form so
this it could be one of those highs
there that we should be looking to push
if you can get a body closure above here
the next candle opens Taps into it and
then runs higher and covers this entire
imbalance and I'm think of 405 is where
it's looking
for right now we traded directly through
the fractal that's fine um we didn't get
a closure until we got below the low of
the fractal see this here pushing up
like that you want to see a run back up
to this High here at
405 and again you're not shorting out of
any of this stuff here because this is
all um not a part of structure
so nice yep yep that that's
it that's what we're looking
for hey BR you enjoy you
enjoy Dave can you show a video on how
to back this the last live stream I did
nice yeah go to go to the last live
stream I um I explained how to back
test but the truth is you should just be
back testing the concepts you you've
learned back test them each session
whatever session you're going to trade
from back test it back test the concept
that you're using
so like I said it should be trading up
above this High
here um with this little tiny fractal
that if we do pull back before it we
could sit
on well there goes a high
now would you more than likely see us do
is take this low right here it happens
that it's imbalance and we know the
first
imbalance puts in another high so you
want to see this close leave that
imbalance open tap back into this
imbalance maybe more or less nearest to
the fractal and then I have another
pushup
got an entry at 17344
beautiful Z in nearest to the fractal
it gets back into this Wick here you
just want to be sure that we don't fail
in here if we end up failing in here
that ends up being a double top in there
that could bring us below this fractal
and then back into that
range so there's
that IM balance top
you know it's funny that this is how
people want to watch
price you know with like all of
this you know uh
uh silence and stuff and I'm just like
you know I get it you you might need to
concentrate you know while you're
trading or while you're pushing a button
and all of that but I've pushed a button
so
much I've watched price so much I've you
know
just engag with it way more than than
you know I've play video games and and
that I've studied other things i' I've
done
so much as it relates to price that I
can be distracted by things I can read
the chat while I'm trading and looking
at Price calling it and listening to
music and checking notification real
quick all of these different things I
can
do because I've done this part of it so
much that's where back testing comes in
some people believe that that you know
if if you uh
uh if you don't back test you could
still make it you could still you need
the real experience you know all of that
other St you need the real experience
none of that is true back testing gives
you the real experience guess what that
same area that you're going through in
back testing somebody got
cooked somebody got
smoked in that same area that you're
back there looking at somebody somebody
got hog washed in this
drop from this high all the way down to
here somebody got smoked thinking
that they were in that move to be the
first people going
up has this happened before yes plenty
of
times plenty of
times so you see what I said so if we
get caught in this Wick we can trade
back into this Wick if we end up getting
stuck in this Wick it's going to come
for the low of the this fractal right
here so you see the low of the fractal
taken
right nice little bounce off of it but
the low of the fractal
taken
now we're
in this down move
here more than likely what you want to
see is let's take the low of that candle
that just closed
tap into this Zone and pop back the
other
way and this is why I talk about if
there's two imbalances after a high is
taken you don't want to consider the
first one you want to consider the next
the the second one nearest to the snd so
this imbalance here you know did give a
nice little pop off of it you know nice
little uh 18-point move off of it um but
I don't trade IM balances anymore I only
trade
utilizing um uh structure zones so what
this is if you guys um watch that video
on Candlestick structure what this is is
that's the high that's the low put in we
traded up Above This Is Us trading back
into that Candlestick structure
flip so that's the only reason why I
would be looking for that low to get
taken out and us going back into this
Z and if we
can get that down candle that pushes in
there you might end up being able
to buy stop back into
sorry back into the
wick up
there so that moves further down into
it I don't know how youall like this
with no
music I figured I'd come out and try
this
but this is just
agonizing guess some people ain't there
yet we they able to just hear noises why
they why they
trading so that's what a successful
candles stick structure flip looks
like we take out that high we trade back
into The Zone and we push back I don't
think we quite delivered the one to one
as of yet um but you see that move right
into the 50% of it and we get that
little push out heading back here the
people who buy stop if we don't trade up
above this down candle High then you're
safe should we end up taking this low
then you know that's something that you
were able to escape without having to
utilize you could move that by stop down
to here
now down to this
high and for me pretty much the the way
that I um
approach prices uh on sweeps
so if they left a wick behind here and
then trade it back below I would be a
part of the move that goes below here
and goes back up for the wick
there so this is not um uh this is an
entry that a lot of people may take
that's fine this is just not one that um
I particular ly uh utilize I pretty much
wait for the sweep and then uh trade
higher but there's the oneto one
delivery uh coming into play bam right
there you
see now the people who got activated in
their buy stop
here this
is smaller Candlestick structure flip
within
here with with this low into this High
then we shift below then we trade out so
now we're back into there for that
confirmation one I don't do confirmation
entries in
downtrends because I'm expecting often
times a sweep of that but being that
this could just
be equal low here that runs back for
this High and the high of that zone too
that's the only reason why I would even
be you know marking something out like
this but that's the entries I choose to
take versus the the um group of entries
that I teach so you see why I talk about
the one: one being something that you
know you should consider because look at
what happens right after the one: one we
deliver the one to one right and then
you see a move back into the range of it
so if you traded from here to the one to
one and you were able to cut on that I
know a lot of people a lot of people are
like oh these are small moves no they're
not this is this is almost 15 points
that you get in a push coming out of
there like
that almost 15 points when when they
Mentor I says five handles for Life he's
talking about Five Points
so these moves are not small you can pay
yourself with things like this look this
is that that uh uh Candlestick structure
move in
here that I mentioned see it pushing
back out like that
again now why am I looking on this side
and why am I not talking
about the Zone that's here why am I not
talking about that
the one to the left why am we not
talking about finding a short way to go
back
below
because what occurred here and how I
mentioned that you want to see those
imbalances forming as we're pushing up
right so it trades back to the origin of
that move and that's the origin of this
push coming out so if there's anything
in there again
for for price to you know move us higher
it would come out of this point of
Interest here and as we mentioned we
could see us go back up to
what that Wick that's above there and
what that would show us
is that there's a low there and there's
a low there and we look to Target that
high and potentially the high of the
Zone because that zone when we went back
up and tapped into it it didn't give us
a new low so that ends up rendering this
Zone within here a weak Zone well it
could it could be you know that that
zone there or potentially this uh up
move here as well so you you might get
another rejection you know somewhere
around here but it could end up looking
for the high of that now how many
entries can I find
within something like
this how many Ines can I
find taking trades off that the first
buy stop that pushed up there right the
second buy stop on the confirmation that
moved up there right the little tap into
the imbalance take a couple points off
of it saw it you know uh uh fail there
and then take the low of the fractal
does not mean we're going lower
does not mean we're going
lower we know we returned to the origin
of that move up now I don't know what's
to the left I don't know if we're
bouncing out something to the left then
the you know there could be some
imbalance there there could be some 4H
hour down candle I don't know I don't
know what's
there but it's based on what you see
price doing now what's the first thing
that I did
when we began to
talk you guys heard me count the swings
right so by the fifth swing I was done
looking for continuations and now was
looking to be on the long side the six
swing we traded up above it no over here
we traded up above it right and then we
came back below it that doesn't
mean that you're wrong
that just means that there's a
possibility that you're early but guess
what the algorithm will still do exactly
what it is scripted to
do whether you were early or
not it would still do
that so you may have people wanting
lower
tell you take out the high of that zone
right particularly this one two I was
seeing at first this this uh the high of
this but like I mentioned there could be
another rejection here before taking
it
so trading literally is about what
what's the first thing that I
noted oh well well 10 10:30 is the next
candle
10 10:30 all right next count is going
to be
10:30 youall hear how the first part of
the trading plan was
created no trades before
10:30 looking at all that's occurring
even if we don't start trading before
10:30 we begin to look at what has
occurred prior to
that then we saw that equal low there we
go okay yeah these are not areas to
Short from here because we're going to
end up going up above this high so that
means you rule out any small fractal
you're choosing inside of there any
small snd you have on the lower time
frame there you're ruling that out so
you don't get cooked by those little
losses we said there' be another
rejection inside of here
right all of these things can be
followed
can be followed can be
predicted the problem is a lot of the
times we're zoomed in like
this we see a large candle come down oh
my goodness oh it's happening Black Swan
is is H is happening y oh oh my is it's
this
happening is is getting ready to take
place y'all I'm telling
you you better hold on to your wigs I'm
tell
this why are we so zoomed in that
close not understanding where these
different things are coming
from where they taking
place and we just follow price that's it
so our money is not in chasing price
higher our money is in getting a
pullback into
continuation based on whatever side it
is that we're on
right so this would end up being this
drop into
here would end up being the first swing
heading
up so why would we be shorting
after only
one wouldn't we be looking for a
pullback into a
move back in
again and that's when you begin to
question why
are we so zoomed into price that any
little candle that forms any any down
candle any up candle that forms we
instantly change our
idea of what we're expecting price to
do what did the plan
say what did the plan say
and the same plan that's on this side
right is the same plan on this side is
it
not so we talked about here the first
imbalance potentially putting in a new
high but if we get stuck in this fror if
we get stuck in that Wick it'll take out
this low right so here's the first
imbalance again did it put in a new high
and anybody running short because they
see a down candle form and they want to
short a pullback why are you on that
side I saw Justin wh say something
earlier today he said that it's the
little losses and I was telling my group
this yesterday so it was funny seeing
that he says the little losses this
chipping away
from the amount you have to
risk there those little tiny unnecessary
losses that's chipping away from
that and yes that's 100% the issue for
people those little
losses you're not a bad Trader you need
better discipline
you know bad
trading you need to be better at
discipline discipline with what your
plan what is your plan according to what
you've learned in back testing according
to it it goes against the tested data
no I asked some people in the group this
week we'll work on it next week but I
ask some people in the group this week I
said what is your plan to get
in what's your trade plan the the very
fourth one the fourth part of your plan
should be
execution and people are telling me my
Concepts also so when we're in a Range
then I got to make sure that you know at
the top of the range that's the only
place that I'm looking for Longs and I'm
not going to hold everything anything in
the middle of the range and then how is
that a plan to get in
how's that BL to find an
entury I told people they need structure
they need narrative then they need their
zones and then they need their their
entry
right I ask somebody what their plan is
they say structure narrative zones and
what so there's there's nothing that
that you can literally spell out to a
12-year-old for them to look at it and
then take an entry somewhere around the
completion of that
plan all the boxes being checked in that
plan you don't have a
plan you cannot get into an entry
without a plan you cannot get into an
entry without a plan you cannot get into
an entry without a plan you cannot get
into an entry without a plan you cannot
get into an entry without a plan a plan
is a plan is not I think it's going to
reject
here you know what's going to be
rejected you're pay
out that's what's going to be
rejected I think it's gonna go down from
here because we still have more you
think
what Market looks at you
like you think you Professor X you you
can move things with your
mind
so it's important to understand that I'm
sure by the time I got down here
everybody's like why is he looking to to
why is he looking to the long side why
is he looking to go long
now and what did I say I said before we
even got
there I said there are people who are
ready to go short and they get pulled
back by 80 something points the other
way because they're ready to go short so
I said what I'm looking for is for a
third higher time frame pullback because
of these lows that are here right
looking for that right closure there so
we get down here it doesn't matter when
I I you know begin to see what I'm
looking for either way I know I'm only
looking for one thing this the move back
into there because the minute I try to
go short from something inside of here
to go down guess what I'm being drawn up
in that higher time frame
pullback and where did that higher time
frame buback go 80 something points the
other
way knowing when to when not
to not saying that people can't find
shorts to continue you
down should that be what price gives
you I don't know if you talked about
this trade I took a short at 10:31
because I focused on structuring had a
one minute Zone 5c flip um because the
higher the Zone got taken out that's
fine you can short or long wherever you
want you just have to know how long you
can hold on to that entry
that's a
okay you took a short that's fine other
people took
along but you have to know how long you
can hold
that and 1 minute 5 second I hope that
you're profitable because if you're not
profitable you should not be on the
5-second time frame
you guys don't have videos of me
teaching you the
5sec none of the accounts that I've I've
I've been running up at all none of the
accounts I've been trading would I've
been trading the 5-second time frame so
for people to not be successful with the
one minute and have this lust for
wanting to be on the 5sec
no become good with the one minute first
and then move down to the lower time
frame anything else is
backwards so you see what we mentioned
here looking for the
pullback down into here
right for what the possibility
of
a move back up into there maybe what is
this they get this fractal yet no not
yet I'm thinking just a little a little
bit lower and then little push off of it
somewhere down
here but you have to know what you're
looking
for
so no the uh Q on Keys No I did not
trade with the Apex payout I did not
trade the 5-second time frame at all I
did not trade the second time frame at
all I was not on the seconds time frame
at
all you do not need the seconds time
frame you need to know where you're
trading from and you need to trust what
you're executing on
that's
it there's nothing else to it and and
the average trade on that was like 10
points this whole this whole move up
here this whole move up here was 80
something
points now couldn't I find an entry to
give me half of that each trade I took
yes yes yes that's possible
yes but what's the sense of
managing a trade to go remember I said
that that I I had a belief that it was
going up above this high
right which that belief is not not is
still still have that belief but imagine
being in an entry somewhere around
here and
I believe that we're going to this High
here
right and I'm let let's say I'm here in
the
entry and now I'm in draw down I'm in
profit now I'm back into draw down then
I'm back into profit and then I'm back
into draw down and then I'm back into
all of this time that's gone by just to
get a TP here
it would be crazy of
me
when it came this
close but because I needed to be right
about seven more points is back to entry
for me
again and how many other entries could I
have found inside of
here how many other moves could I have
taken
in there and and been right
about and paid
myself that same
amount just from knowing where to begin
scalping where to begin whether it's
with the trend counter Trend doesn't
matter which
one I just know what what is occurring
here easy to spot
top of the
range bottom of the range is
accumulation knowing where to get in
knowing when to knowing when not
to I always get lost in overanalyzing
that's because you too zoomed in
there's the problem you two zoomed
in is the stream going to stay public
afterwards yes it
is yeah you you two zoomed
in 100% that's your
issue do zoom in
likewise that's a lot of people's
issue you think
that you need to
be
facing the candles like this and you'd
be interpreting every little thing
inside of
here when there are things
that have already occurred
right there are things that already
occurred that'll give us the
understanding of of what's potentially
getting ready to occur next and we would
just wait on
that wait on that right so what's a
simple example of
that this high right here whatever this
is taing into below more than likely it
often looks to go back and take out that
previous high right
there and that'll run right back to this
fractal with the possibility of taking
out the high of the fractal because
of this Zone above here not entirely
being
mitigated so we we have that we we have
that that little
understanding of that and if if that's
what we believe is going to occur if
we're on the lower second if we're on
the the the lower time frame we're on
the second time frame and we see our uh
uh seconds uh confirmation within here
then we trade
that if we're willing to take whatever
is here to the left and utilize trading
off of that then we trade
that but regardless of what it is we
have to be willing to accept what the
loss behind that that area we're
choosing to trade from except that this
is our uh um um take profit or or this
is what we're looking for to looking to
occur and when this happens we need to
know where we are exiting not trying to
a lot of people ask me this question how
do you
manage um how do you manage your stop
losses
like how do you
Trail your stop losses I Trail my stop-
losses by taking
profit that's how I try my stop
losses I try my stop losses by taking
profit
so
again pay yourself
um guys you recommend college and trade
or just trade you should do college
defin if you're in college do college
definitely
100% because if trading doesn't work out
for you you have something to fall back
on so College
100% it teaches you how to complete
something it teaches you how to finish
something College taught me a lot was it
needed for me
no because I don't currently use the
degree but it taught me how to learn
properly that's what it did it taught me
how to learn
properly so if if
that's you know something that you still
struggle with with learning then then
you know you need to learn and
successfully complete something
you learn and successfully complete
something I left College last year I
mean hey it's not for everybody you
know uh this DRS are distracting your
mouth is distracting uh what was your
degree in uh
psychology uh been taking 10 points for
this Market beautiful
um that's too far away please zoom in
put your glasses on when the mentorship
reopen I'm not too sure
yet um I Heard somewhere you recommend a
profitable loser everywhere I recommend
the profitable
loser
uh let me see how do you know it is
accumulation because I am he the master
back tester
um let me
see how not to get lost I told you that
zoom out make sure you zoom out
uh let me
see how do proper plan looks like um you
got to find it in back
testing cover the kids
is Target
filled
um always confused with counter swing
since as count seven well you got to
know that they're from different time
frames so that's your problem you're not
counting um
from one specific time
frame this feels like House of no music
that is true but you know this is
something that people need to
see um that I'm saying this
beforehand and we're watching it do it
and then we're seeing the completion of
it and I'm giving all the wise for it
and I'm telling people how they
should look to set their entries up and
where they should look to take profit
and you know all of those different
things I'm I'm teaching it in real time
it's not just going over something in
past price action oh I want to see a low
get taken hey nobody care about that I
don't have enough money for a high and
low to be taken I want to show you
what's happening now and here's why I
believe it and here's what I think it's
going to happen and here's because
because I the thing is going to happen
not because I'm trading what I think
it's because I've tested and verified
this over and over and over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over I've watched this more than you've
watched TV I've watched this more than
you play video games so I know beyond
the shadow of a doubt whatever it is
that I see occurring whatever it is that
I believe is occurring I know that I'm
going to trust that over trusting you
us3 is about to dump and then you watch
it pump 100 points into your
nostrils because what
you thinking that something is going to
happen versus you verifying in price
that this is something that occurs
right so
I I told yall y you gota you gotta
accept you got to accept the law you got
to accept what what it is you're you're
wagering you got to accept the fact that
this this is your target you got to
accept the fact that this is how you
you're anticipating your setup to
occur if you have not verified these
things in back testing you can never
trust them in forward
testing some of y'all just want a
forward test and not back test okay
that's
fine somebody told me I was a white
supremacist because I told them they
need to back test the question they
asked
me now back testing is a racial slur
crazy
right
so you know you you need to back test
more than you forward test back testing
is more important than forward
testing back testing is more important
than forward testing you're not going to
hear a lot of people tell you
that but you're also not going to hear a
lot of people say the things I say every
day is a trading day every day is a
profitable day it's a blessing be on the
right side of the market you're not
going to hear people talking like
that you're not going to hear people you
know something happened overnight
everybody's like oh trade demo today
because the price action is going to be
don't you dare because we we it's so
much uncertainty Israel Obama Iran and
y'all so addicted to trading it's Friday
you should go and and and you should you
should be studying you should not want
to have to just push the button all the
time that's an addiction you and they
projecting all of that on
you when it's the same stuff occurring
each and every day how dare you say it's
an algorithm and you act like it's it's
going to do something
different scriptures do one thing and
only one
thing and when you see that thing you
know you saw him back testing time and
time and time again
that's where your profitability
is
right that's where your profitability
is what do you think of today's
quarterly Theory um
I wish him a quadrennial year I don't
know anything about
that instead of saying Happy New Year to
people now I'm say happy quadral
year hopefully I'm right I don't know
anything about
that when does the one to one fail why
you don't want to back to us how about
you go and back to us and see when it
fails you just going to ask questions
all the time AP trades what's up baby
um I'm telling them
back
test oh no that that's that's not the AP
trades we talking about hold up that's
that's a fool my
bad wrong wrong wrong AP trades look at
this look at
this oh is that the right AP trades I
don't I don't know I'm
I'm very difficult decision should we
chat should we block him or should we
which what should we do chat
should should we block him chat or or
she that's not AP trades that's PA
trades that's his
cousin trying to see with the chat
trying to give me to do let me let me
put up a let me put up a uh a poll real
quick hold on oh
I hit the wrong button sorry
ap3 never mind no poll anymore
so this this is this is what you know I
I want you guys to to
consider remember what I
said I said that when we begin that
accumulation I started off in this in
this
video talking about it you guys go back
into the video you hear me
discussing I started off
saying how to trade accumulation now
accumulation what we're discussing is
what happens from higher time frame to
lower time frame
right that's what we're talking about
it's not something that's restrictive to
this one time
frame accumulation is the same kind of
accumulation on all time frames not just
to this one time frame so what we talked
about here
is the accumulation above right here
right so what we should be expecting or
anticipating
is when we open up it let's say let's
say we leave this Wick here when we open
up we should be looking for price to
trade at least back to this fractal
right or slightly up above it and then
shift back into the range
for
Monday if it closes like
this we should be anticipating that
based on the area that we're tapping
into to the left
right and we know that we just took a a
low
right and we know all Concepts work
right so here we have the support and
resistance this is prior support turn
resistance so we would be looking for
the retest of this previous support turn
resistance right so that's one thing
two we should be looking at Price taking
a low and rebalancing to an fvg right
this ICT concept whatever we should be
looking at dtfa of course you know with
the the zones that we in we anticipating
price to trade you know out of this snd
response but at least above the previous
candles
this is a daily time frame that we're
we're now you know forecasting some of
this
stuff we know that this is a four candle
drop based on a daily right so if this
is a four candle drop based on a
daily then what we're looking for is the
people that go long from here we know
there's a possibility that price takes
them out first and then trades in the
other way to take the high out that was
put in so whether that high goes above
the previous candle High whether it runs
into the fractor just just up above what
we're anticipating for the day right or
or maybe not even the day let's say the
day Clos as a doy the following day can
run to that
high and then you got people going oh
the high of the week putting on Tuesday
and then the L you know all of those
different things that are in
there which which they all you know sort
of work
out uh uh the same
way but
but we would essentially be considering
that because what we also know that we
at the bottom of a
range we know Long's in the bottom of
the range
right so it means Monday into Tuesday
you could have that
run going back into the range going back
to retest to whatever it is going back
to rebalance going whatever it is it's
doing
you go to the weekly time frame you know
the weekly time frame the weekly candle
could open put in a wick here and then
what the that's for the the uh the P3
Bros then what put in a body like
that and then have a
wick just below it like that
next candle TS back into the wick follow
candle moves up like that above the
previous week's high
now tons of stuff you could anticipate
you can you can think
of you see
happening but some people just have no
real material materialization of of
getting into the trade getting into the
move so
remember what I said I said that we
often get the sweep of that low right
and when we get the sweep of that low
what you tend to see is
that when price leaves a little Wick
behind
here often times what we're anticipating
is for price to run back to it and
potentially take the high of it right so
there's a a a ton of
reasons
why you know we can be getting into
little entries to
scalp and little areas that we we you
know are Nimble on in terms of taking
profit
and it's just that it has to be a part
of our
plan it must be a part of our plan must
number one it must be a part of our
plan
so there goes my low
there previous candle's high is
here you the bullish close above could
run right into that Wick right there
right and with that you have to know
beyond a shadow of a doubt that you've
seen
it in order to take part in it
in order to trade it like you know you
you
know that St price hit there there a
possibility of giving you a heat heat a
TP look at that that's a dyslexia
possibility of giving you TP
there at at this this high but most
importantly it could just be looking to
run back
into that zone there
right there so we got a
sweep on the lower time frame
here and if we can get up above this and
close then we can run to that high there
and it's as simple as
that so what is it it do if it gets into
here you know there's a possibility of
rejecting back
into whatever Zone it would have created
below and if that's enough to take price
higher Above This Wick that's what it
does if it's not then it struggles in
there and then puts in another
low but you have to know how it looks
from lower time frame to high higher
time frame so what do we have on a lower
time frame here what we have is these
swings right we have
one we have two we have three we have
four we have
five so we have five swings that are
currently on this lower time frame
heading down so the same thing that we
mentioned here moving down into here and
then you begin to see price move
sideways here and you begin to see price
move back up above there the same exact
thing
here so here would essentially be
waiting to capitalize on that moment of
running back into the previous
range and there's several techniques
that I've shared in the dis I mean in
the Discord on YouTube the several
techniques that I've shared on how
to get into an entry specifically video
7 and video 8 but y'all don't like to
read y'all don't like to watch y'all
don't like to write but y'all expect to
learn it
just it it is beyond me you don't want
to read you don't want to write you
don't want to watch but you think you're
going to
learn that's why I told a young man to
ask about college go
to
college it will teach you how to
learn go to
college so there's
the six swing
there and you see
it wicking up
six swing there you could look for it to
move back above these highs and I
still have us looking to get back into
this wake
here
so you have to learn how to
learn you cannot think that you could
sit there and watch a 27 minute video
and all of a sudden you're
profitable because you still got to
watch it in real time and guess what
those videos they're in real
time they're in real time go and look at
somebody's back tested video and then go
and try to replicate it I promise you
you're still not going to be
profitable you are still not going to be
profitable still not going to be
profitable oh you stole so and so you
just doing the Quasi Moto so you knew
about the Quasi Moto all these years and
you still struggling with profitability
what's up with
that I wasn't I wasn't profitable off of
the Quasi motor I was profitable off of
trend lines what's up with
that what's up with that you KN you knew
all this time about that what's up with
that
you know all of these
strategies you know who stole what but
you can't use it
yourself oh that's right you you just
the the trading encyclopedia
okay you just your trading
encyclopedia and everybody else that
comes around what do they want to
do they want to reinvent the wheel but
they don't know how to
drive going reinvent the wheel
yet you don't know how to
drive something is up with
that reinvent the
wheel don't know how to
drive so that's why I don't listen to
people who who say other things about
other strategies and oh well this is
going to do that because if you look at
this and then pair it with the
fundamentals with that and then do that
and then that's not going to change my
idea of what I believe price is doing
what I believe price is going to
do that is not going to change my I
could tell you that
much that is not going to change my
idea of what I believe price is going to
do because what I've seen in back
testing is
enough them trend lines work and people
still giving Tor shape that's because
people are ignorant people think that
just because they have strategies that
could lower their
risk to far less of a risk than a trend
line can or a triangle can or a channel
can or whatever it is or or the support
and resistance can they think that
because they have these strategies that
could lower their risk a lot more they
look down on everybody
else and it's funny
because now that the ICT Community is
seeing a lot of this
you know stuff that we're doing take you
know take on a lot of popularity and
stuff they're upset that we always
mention and troll their
strategies but if you listen to what
they do to other people it is a terrible
thing most of it not all of it because
there's other people who you know act
like strategy leaders too but most of it
comes from that
Community most of it comes from the ACT
community unfor
most of
it so for us we
we you know make certain to let people
know every strategy can
work it's
you that doesn't work every strategy out
there can
work it's you it's you it's you
and and we'll show alongside this is
what I love that stoic does we'll show
alongside how all of these
things
work we'll show you channels we'll show
you trend lines we'll show you you know
all of that other good stuff we we show
you all
that trust and believe we're going to
show it to
you we'll show you every bit of
it and show you how you you can put it
all together but you got to start with
one
thing you got start with one
thing and you work your way
out but if you're not good at one thing
you're not going to be good at anything
that's why we prioritize
structure
right so guys look why why am I not
shorting through this
why am I looking to go short in
that well based on what was said
already what we were
anticipating
right was for price to move back into
the other
end to a particular
area after something occurred to the
left
that's what we were
anticipating so at any
point we saw the pop run up above
that that uh um those highs in
there we show us run right to that line
and what we we stopped yeah we
anticipated price to take take out the
high of
it
but it's not our job to be 100% right
about what price is
doing it's our job to understand what
price is doing and find a way to get
involved find a way to get
involved so what we have
here is the same thing we met mentioned
over here
right I move up until I move down we
trade higher we go back there and then
we had a little push off of there right
and then the same thing happened inside
of here
right this move up we trade down we push
higher we go back here we trade higher
right
go down go up BR down trade higher go
back into this move and then we trade
higher right same thing
happening right same thing
happening
over and over again and all it is is up
to us to
find an opportune
time to be able to end enter into the
market enter into the market
right and take something off the table
take something out of
there take a little profit off
of table rather than being right about
whether a weekly draw is going to happen
rather than being right about whether a
daily whatever is going to
happen just a couple minutes a day
couple minutes a
day and there will be times that we are
wrong that's
fine but if we continue to execute based
on what our plan tells us to
do then
Viola we in there like
swimwear what do you about the new
Futures I don't know nothing about prop
firms don't ask me anything about prop
firms um the good old question are you
trying to be right 100% of the time are
you trying to make money and I ask that
question all the time because it's a
question that's
true you want to be right or you want to
make money which
one which
one which one matters more you want to
be right you want to make money
the question is
simple and you're greed
is you know something that
determines the outcome of
that say I've been a longtime follower
of I I was terrified by yesterday's I
breing so I I watched it a little bit he
was explaining some things you know on
on some other pairs like da and and he
was also teaching yesterday I was
teaching too you know I was teaching
about something entirely different of
course but I was teaching yesterday as
well and maybe it's in an environment
where it's best for him to
teach you know there there are some
environments that I really don't like to
trade in in in super trending
environments I'll take a step
out I honor my experience and take a
step out
in in trending
environments maybe in more or less
ranged environments he he wants to take
a step
back I can understand
that and would would prefer to to uh uh
teach so you know with that it it's just
whatever the strong suit is of of the
Traer itself
what will you do if trading won't be
allowed anymore um trading is how the
whole world is
ran like you got to remember these these
um these things that we're looking at
like we have um you know oil over here
we have gold here you we have wheat we
have rice got y'all have y'all seen
Rice have have
y'all sto over here talking about I was
I was sharing rice proper Ganda with
y'all no have y'all seen
rice listen I was buying up some R
that's why I got this area here I was
buying up some rice in in that area
there buying up some
rice because what you see is is I was
watching for rice to go higher up above
this
high that high right there 2023
high and we have R dro a little lower I
was a little afraid you know I I was
going Target
filled I was I was going to get out of
my my
trade right here I start selling rights
on eBay but nothing you know uh
um we we held the zone you see it 50% of
the Zone we held it and look at how rice
is right back up here again we have
plenty of videos on YouTube and
following rice
so Ry has a possibility of of getting
back up to that that 2020 high and I
mean that's going to be
expensive so I enter my position here in
my
garage quite a bit of bags of rice in
here into my position here
and do you see that
we're back up to here again I told you
guys start buying up some of these
things these these uh uh you know things
that that do not expire you know as fast
as fruit or find ways to preserve them
or or whatever it
is find ways to preserve
them because when prices get higher
you're not caught
in you
know now needing to pay a lot more for
something that two weeks ago you paid a
lot less
for two weeks ago you paid a lot less
for
it we actually might be looking for that
48 up there on enq um two weeks ago you
paid a lot less for it but look at that
it had this move down back in here hit
the 50% of the Zone there my stop loss
was right behind here because then I've
been in and draw down because I was
buying from down
here and look at that move
higher that's going to cost
somebody but I know I got enough rice
for got enough right for them to take
that that high there and then drop back
into the Zone there and now you know
prices cool down again now we can add
into our
position before possibility of it
spiking up
again well maybe when it take that you
drop right back into the 50% of the Zone
here so may we get back to the
entry I'm going to have another pump off
of it but if it's a strong Trend what
you see is price pop out of here and
continue higher you won't see it get
back to the
50% is a strong trend
so long as we get a double top somewhere
in here then that's where we could run
that low that we put in after this high
is taken and then potentially look to
Target this low too hopefully you know
it's it don't go down that way where
price runs higher because it's going to
hurt a lot of
people but these charts are not just for
taking little small entries off and
taking little trades off
of oh yes I want it my TP hit no this is
for planning your
life you've access to this data to plan
your
life there 48 look look like we still
going above to that 48
right so let me let me put an alert
there the
48 you been putting alarm there
it let us know when it gets
there
because somebody went
short gold tapped into the previous
day's high after taking the
low um
gold oh yeah gold had that extension
overnight that was a news from Iran and
Israel Israel had
um bombed Iran same thing with this here
too uh oil oil had that same push
overnight as
well I was talking to my kid and I was
teaching them how
to spot some of this stuff and trade it
and I said listen this is oil like oil
real time yeah it's oil you can trade
oil so he like how you know when it's
going to go up and down
well here's the
thing I don't want to brag but but then
I realized I was talking to my kids so I
was like hold on let me let me let me
take you take you in I say you see this
move going up into this move going down
that area that it leaves behind as a
Zone like that open space yeah there a
zone are there any zones down there I
said yeah there's some zones down there
too but what we focusing on is this when
we get there you know when to short to
take price down when we get there you
know when the long to take price up and
all it depends on is how much you think
is enough when you do take these entries
but you got to know where to get in when
to get it so this oil right before
stream I had marked this up I was like
go right there and then you going to see
it move away from
there i' been confident talking to my
kid I'm like Hey listen you think it's
going to go down up let's let's make a
bet let's make a
bet you know them cookies you bought
you the organic chocolate chip cookies
let's make a bet about
it I'm fan competition ain't that
unfair
competition hey look at that yo price
price just they they just don't want me
to
win so let me move them and take profit
up they just don't want me to
win so yeah is it's
um but you still trade those news with
your rules I don't know what you talking
about um you shouldn't trade any news at
all that's what I personally
think no
news yes I was I was hustling the kid I
knew I had the upper hand I knew I had
the upper
hand and every time I eat those cookies
all you hear is nothing but complaints I
don't even eat a lot of them I just eat
like one or two it's called Dad tax but
you know they they
don't they don't understand that you got
to pay taxes in
life they learn
soon that's exactly what they call me
Cookie Monster you've been
listening bab you don't have enough
rights to put in a new H listen soon
enough I am going to have have enough RS
stoic with this
this with this orange juice he's been
sharing orange juice propaganda for the
last few
weeks when is orange
juice you can get your vitamin C other
ways when you hungry juice don't
matter you want that food to fill up the
belly
right I didn't say fill it out I said
fill it up you want food to fill up the
belly you want food
to fill it up right somebody said we
need a music break so hold on y'all when
I'm wrong I usually turn on the music
so what
look at how they keep rejecting there
support and resistance right
[Music]
there's something about
you makes me want to
retire want to feel something
true Can You Feel
My I'm a strer to
[Music]
the to
late this guy is so disgustingly
arrogant you Lumi you still out there
Shilling alt coins you gu go look at his
go look at his Twitter profile still
chilling alt coins
what you
doing get your life you Lumi this guy is
so disgustingly arrogant but you got to
watch me on TV
[Music]
right don't watch me watch TV oh wait my
bad Target
fil
[Music]
take Hey listen I I don't know I don't
know why they come in here all the time
you know
I'm making noise you could even let them
hear my TP
here you you couldn't even always coming
and making a noise what's up with
[Music]
that tell me what I
do you take me hey C baby what's up
[Music]
oh
yeah look where we are
now how you
see we our heart
out to find some
Rel I going to calm
down I just want to be
with nobody else
now I just want to
[Music]
leave take me high
take me
high take me high
[Music]
all right all right let's let's bring it
in let's bring it in your Lumi just
threw us for a loop let's let's bring it
in just do us for a loop I'm I'm I'm
sorry y'all I'm trying to be a little
more professional these days but they
just come on in and
and they
just I don't know they you know what you
know what I think it is they they
probably some felons out there they they
on house
arrest so they ain't got nothing better
to do
da da
da I learned how to measure before I
knew what was I sing sleep
do treat sadness a smile you can't have
what's next till you hang with it for a
while this is house
arrest come we your Sunday
Best this is house arrest
[Music]
I Lear me I knew was I you sleep do you
like
my
[Music]
sadile come to we your Sunday
F this is how
this
[Music]
is
this come to wear your Sunday
F this
[Music]
house all right let me bring it in right
let me bring it in I'm trying to be more
professional these days
I'm probably anybody and any
professional coaches here y'all got to
teach me how to do this
thing so how to be how to be
professional yo anybody can recommend me
to
someone hi a lot of
people I how to tell them a lie and make
them think is the truth so they would
feel good about it rather than learning
uncomfortable truths about themselves
and about what they're doing and can can
anybody got anybody got a coach for me
coach need a
[Music]
[Applause]
coach this
is this is
[Music]
all right all right all right so I I
think that this is
um a perfect way to and I did tell y'all
I said um we get back above here I said
once we get into this Zone here you more
than likely see a rejection within here
and that rejection will let us know you
know whether price wants to trade higher
to here now it would be pure greed to be
in an entry here and go to try and
Target this High here be pure greed why
because there's no structural shifting
that's taking place as of yet what do I
mean by that I mean that as we're
putting in these highs and lows heading
up right we put in that low we put in
this low here put another high here when
we trade it below here there's no body
closure below this low so this high is
not
validated so what we had was a quick
shift below and the body pulled back
up so that right there becomes a down
candle that took a low that could send
price higher and what take out the high
that's not a part of structure so what
did we go and do
we trade it up to tap onto
What tap onto the low that did produce a
high right you see this this High missed
it let me just move some of these
drawings
out this oh come
on this High missed it right
here that high missed it but this High
hit it
so what it's actually hitting
is that little tiny Zone inside of there
tapped right into it you see another
move down now this
becomes the validated high right sorry
the the protected high and this was a
validated low moving back into that why
is it a validated low because it put in
a low and closed up above the previous
candle's high now putting in a low and
closing up above the previous previous
candles high does not mean that because
this low traded below the previous low
and did not close that doesn't classify
as a low it could still classify as a
low if it moves up and puts in a closure
above that high then you see us move
back down below it so all all we're
doing
is when we're focusing on these swings
heading down this just becomes the third
swing in this down move right here so
you in anticipate through here another
move back into there and should we get
stuck putting an equal low here then you
can see that go back up to take out this
high and why would it take out that high
because that high into that low right
here remember what we talked
about the larger structure we were
following right the larger structure we
were following so we know that this
could in turn move back up to put in a
fourth High we have one we have two we
have three so four to six then we expect
price to reverse right so we're still
trading down into this this structure we
came out of but what we're following is
the higher time frame highs and lows and
what we're taking little entries off of
are what makes up those higher time
frame highs and lows because what
happens is if we end up taking a short
out of these areas look at how long you
stay around in in that short before
price actually leaves the area and then
when price gets down here and moves back
up to there again now it's just right
back to your entry or right near your
entry for you to want to get price to
push away potentially if you're
targeting this sell side right here
you would take some time in that
entry rather than just being able to
find these little moves within price and
you can create your own 100 Point moves
inside of here you don't need to be a
part of a move that you held it all the
way for 100 point you can create that
for
yourself you know and I think that's the
the the demons that a lot of people
fight they want more but they don't
understand that they can create more if
they learned more right you can create
more if you learn more you never need to
be a part of holding the move from the
top other people other systems they
might do that stuff and some days when
they can't find a move that delivers
that they're out of the market every day
you can find a move utilizing what it is
that we teach here every
day no matter what's happening in the
market oh this is a bad day to trade
because what something happened in
another country and we have no idea
what's what the response is going to
going to
be okay and and if you go back if you
let's let's go back to
to let's go back to Dow
Jones oh we have we had no idea you kof
was going to take place but was that
tradeable coming out of it yes oh we we
had no idea that the 2008 crash going to
take did did we did we come out of that
too oh we had no
idea Black Monday and all that other
stuff is is take but but did we come out
of there was there a way to trade our
way out those large moves they're not
for us that's not our money in those
large moves but we need to understand
that every time those things
happen we have opportunity now but
should we be highly leveraged and fatten
up at this High we lose
everything going that way
everything because we want higher prices
price dips back and then trades up above
trades right back above there Taps back
into it and then trades higher that's
the thing that we mentioned on
rice has the possibility of taking that
high tapping back in and then trading
higher on
Rice you do that with gold do that with
whatever it is that that's connected to
your daily living so it's time for you
to learn what you need to learn and do
what you have to do so you can do what
you want to
do and I I'll continue to say it over
and over again fast scalping sorry is
the fastest way to to any sort of
acceleration of
wealth scalping learning how to scalp
this is one of the most liquid markets
in the world yet people think they need
to be in a move from up here holding the
move all the way from up
here and they need to be in it heading
all the way down to this low like you
some Allstar fund manager that
that you know you you trying to win an
award for who held who held the entry to
longest who made the most money for no
you're trying to save your life you're
trying to save
yourself that's what it is is is it's in
the details of these things that you're
going to learn how to operate within the
details of
them and then what what's that part of
risk management that we talked about the
part risk management that we talked
about was paying yourself that needs to
be a
Cornerstone a
Cornerstone in your risk management a
Cornerstone needs to be to pay yourself
you don't have to be a part of every
single move that's inside of here you
never need to be a part of every single
move you can
find you you can just find yourself in
one or two moves take little short
scalps within
there and and walk out for the day I had
a guy in the Discord that said he was up
$620 on a
day yeah I'm going to come back in an
hour for what you should come back
tomorrow because if you go out there you
have no credentials you have no skill
you have no degrees that's going to
support a job ever paying you
$620 for the little bit of minutes you
traded to make this so come back
tomorrow that's
greed I I don't know if he came back
tomorrow I can't you tell you what
happened I hope he listened you
know but you can find these little
things within
price pay yourself more than a job would
ever pay you what whatever skill or
credential you have and then just come
back the next day
was 400 bucks today and 400 bucks
tomorrow 400 bucks each day two 300
bucks each day what's that that replaces
your entire
salary
so that should always be the
goal you know and you don't have to be a
part of everything to make that just
simple things know when we're in a Range
trade based on a
range have clear
exits and say hey this is enough no job
would ever pay me more than this so I'll
come back to work
tomorrow
right and you know that that solves a
lot of your your financial hardship and
now you get to focus on life
now you get to focus on cleaning those
things up that you've been carrying that
you have not even been able to stop and
address whether it's things at home with
your partner whether it's things with
your kids whoever it is you have enough
time now to stop and deal with
them before they get
worse cuz life is not about
money it's about the time that you spend
with your loved ones the time you spend
with your Offspring whoever it is the
time you spend with those close to you
that's what life is about because when
you're
gone tomorrow that same bus that you
take to work the same train you take to
work the same same you know workplace
you you show up to to do what you have
to do the same news channels you love to
watch that movie that was schedule for
next week guess what it's still going to
show up it's still going to keep running
that movie is still going to drop
whether you dead or alive but guess
whose World
changes guess who whose World changes
the people you left
behind the people you left
behind I don't have enough money to die
and have my kids never depend on anybody
else
again I don't have enough possessions to
die and my kids never depend on anybody
else again that's the goal in life I
don't care if I have to die trying I
don't care if I don't get to rest while
in pursuit of
it they should never have to depend on
anybody else for shelter they should
never have to depend on a job to pay
them peanuts and treat them like their
mules
they should have choice in what they
want to do in life what they love to do
how they want to give back to
humanity so that's the drive for me
that's what keeps me coming back and I
know there's people out there in
financial hardship that can't get those
things that's why I do these live
streams that's why I come out here and
teach yeah I'm disgusted by the public
and the trading space but guess what
it's still my duty to help somebody else
be able to help themselves to help
somebody else be able to help their kids
what good is it for my kids to live a
comfortable life and their friends
struggle or people their age they run
into and have issues with because of
whatever it is basic
needs basic
needs we talking about being okay with
kids in poverty kids not being able to
eat kids and and and parents yeah some
parents are the the problem for that but
those things are
generational somebody's willing to break
that curse somebody's willing to get out
of
that and that's what brings you here to
these streams whether you like to hear
me or
not that's what brings you
here this might be pushing back up into
that previous high that it put in the
little shortterm high
that's what brings you
here and you got to put in that
time because you owe it to the people
around you just like I feel as though I
owe it to mankind I owe it to others to
do it it's my duty to do
it you know you you have everything here
everybody's course is leaked
I mean I don't have a course they're
just live streams they leaking and me
yelling at people but you that's what
they want to Ed to learn again
everybody's stuff is
leaked all the information in the world
you have and you can still sit there and
act like you need more it's all out
there but it's you you need you this
time you are Enigma I say that all the
time not my Concepts not anybody else's
Concepts
you you are Enigma you need you you
don't need me your family needs you they
don't need
me and when you put in that time you're
going to see that you're able to do
this you can do this trust me you can
it's all in your head trying to lie to
you and tell you you can't no you can
but you got to have more discipline than
you currently have now
so hope you guys uh enjoyed this uh this
stream and I'm going leave youall on
this
[Music]
bang the storm is over you made it St
I've come to find you're what I want so
I laugh about it my tears are dry don't
doubt about it I'll be all right my pass
behind me I'm Let It Go and all that I
know it's going to be
better it's going to be
better it's s with
together it's going to be
better it's going to be better now going
to be better now it's going to be better
now it's going to be better now
[Music]
it's it's going to be
better it's going to be
better
I'm
found
found all right y'all listen I know I
was I wasn't supposed to do streams uh
in April because you know my kid is off
of school so um I got permission don't
worry I got permission but
um I'm probably going to slow down on a
lot of public engagement you got people
like Charles he's running um his free
Discord right now people like sto you
talk on um Twitter with you know just
join the gang look for the DTF X hashtag
and just follow everybody that that's a
part of it you might got some you might
have some weirdos there you know that's
fine you have weirdos in every
discipline might have some weirdos there
but um you know partner up with some of
these people you're not alone you're not
by yourself so I'll catch up with you
guys later all right peace out
[Music]
y'all it's going to be
as long as we're
together it's going to be
better it's going to be better
[Applause]
[Music]
now it's going to be better
now oh long as we together