e
[Music]
you bring
the you bring the love that I
need you
you bring the love that I need feeling
that's so real you
bring you bring the love that I need you
bring the feeling so you bring the you
bring the love that I need
you feeling so real
[Music]
youing the
I you
bring you bring the love that I need
feeling so
youing you bring the love that
I you bring the
you bring the love that I feel
[Music]
so bring
the you bring the love that I
need you bring the he
you bring the love that I need feeling
that's so real you bring the you bring
the love that I need you bring the
feeling so real you
bring you bring the love that I made you
bring the feeling so real you bring the
you bring the love that I need you bring
the feeling so real you bring the you
bring the love that I you bring the
feeling Let Go
[Music]
real you the love that I need
you bring
me you bring the love that I feeling
next
[Music]
you you bring the
I you
bring you bring the that I
feeling
you you bring the love that I
you bring
me you bring the love that I feeling so
for
[Music]
all right what's up y'all what's
up morning morning what's up
y'all let me bring down the music
some so
um I hope everybody's good
U um you see this here because we put
this level
in the group
uh in the spam section now we put that
level there you guys already know I'm
looking for this
here the beginning of that Wick even
if dodgy has the high being taken
out I'm still looking for the beginning
of the week there um that's usually my
exit
um and speaking of uh exits I'm
actually uh let me see I'm actually in
on this right
here sorry this is where it
started you guys can see this right this
this is where the entry
started right here right at that 42 it
was actually 3 9 but it didn't give me
an opportunity to get in that 39 is
something um that I alerted the Discord
on um because of our previous range down
below here and that 39 is where I was
sorry looking for the long and I was
looking for price to at least just
deliver the one to one so the one: one
is at this high right
here looking for price to at least
delivered a one to one there and um that
was about 78 points away as you guys see
this 39 to this
117 you know quite a bit of points away
but when we have this news Wick here we
know that price often times come comes
back to Target the beginning of that
Wick
so that just extends it you know um you
know just a little more just based on
narrative or so uh but it's a nice
little uh Banger right there
uh that
was uh
called for you
guys
um let me just show you guys where I'm
at now I'm actually
gonna have this position
closed I'm going to close this position
but I'm right
here this is still from the same low
the same load that was down there being
able to just ride that on up because you
know it's delivering the higher time
frame one to one there right the zone
right there 50% there you know it's
delivering at one to one so you ride it
up but these circumstances show trading
back into this direction we know news
happened here so often times what do we
do we go and grab that news Wick so what
do you usually Target the beginning of
that news Wick cuz you're not always
entirely sure that the news Wick will be
taken just like down
here dodgy could tell you that sometimes
they don't take the
wick this is the news wig down below
right here
right there's the news Wick there's the
beginning of the wick as the exit right
right there there's that clean exit but
it doesn't take that low and imagine
being at break even all the way up here
some somewhere in this region here and
it not taking that and going right back
to your entry are you kidding me you got
to be out of your mind I'm
not not the bag hold it type so
um that was a nice
little
uh nice little long we
rode to the
top
um and when when this kind of extension
happens here when this kind of extension
happens here like that your business is
below here if it retraces and above here
should price take the high anything in
between that you're not trying to take
part in this entry here to go further to
take this high right here you're not
trying to fight this this high in here
to go in short down below
um you know you don't pick up a mindset
to do any of that unless obviously your
your plan has showed up what are you
exactly shorting up here if you were to
short I think for me I saw a five minute
oh there we go the the flag handle there
there we go so um you know we obviously
hit that there so that warrants that
move back into this range you know that
this um first balance could very well
put in a new high above this high so you
still don't want to uh pick up that
insatiable desire to short when price is
clearly still moving in the the the
upward direction we have quite a bit of
swings here though uh one two three this
would be the fourth one if it takes this
high right here um so it's quite a bit
of swings on this extension up but I
would be expecting price to um take that
high up
there that the news Wick high so if you
weren't able to find your opportunity
within here I'm sure dodgy got in right
here because that's the Run of his lows
right the Run of um you know the draw
was Asia so there's his imbalance that
forms price closes up above the high of
the imbalance I'm sure his little
partial points like along these Wicks
here and then his Terminus
is the the high up there as well
so uh you know many different people see
uh different reasons as to why they
would get into an opportunity to Target
anything to the upside but for me um you
know this is always going to be it price
Taps right into my zone and trades right
into the previous range so um or
delivers that one to one on that high
now just because the one: one is here
does not mean that your stop loss has to
be all the way down here for your entry
to be
here this is just the invalidation of
the idea but the idea can come from down
here and make its way up to deliver that
now like that it can come from lower
down here but the invalidation of the
idea would be behind that zone there but
you see price just perfectly tapped on
to 39 uh and and you know ran out of
there so
uh it was a dead giveaway uh when it
came to uh Market
open so I'm just waiting
to waiting for that
delivery um like I said at least to here
uh this
58 and then potentially the the high up
above
so hope you guys are able
to capitalize on
that because I know I
did Target filled
maybe there we go it is
Terminus mentorship students know that
kind of
exit that I tend to make make especially
when we form that candle there the exit
that I'm making is right up above that
candle because price can take out the
high of that and then go back below it
and why do I want to sit in all of that
just for continued delivery might as
well just step out at the the you know
highest point of volume before it begins
to lean to the other
side so yeah that that was a nice uh
nice little delivery somebody said it
was news or something like that I didn't
I didn't see that and they the um was it
9:45 I didn't see that any the
candlesticks maybe it wasn't a high
impact oh okay it was it was a orange
fold there
all right PMI still below expansion
levels but still above
expectations and consumer sentiment will
see what they give us but that that was
a nice uh little run there
um to
that wake up
above I guess this is that consumer
sentiment candle
and guys do do you do you need any more
of that like do you do would I really
need to to get more as much as I can to
have the highest and the most in the you
know it really doesn't make
sense you know especially if you're in
from a move down here being Nimble here
and not having a habit of trying to push
this right here will say to you guys a
lot of losses a lot of break evens not
Target getting that right
there so nice consumer sentiment just
you know ran us up above that which is
great um I did have a price going
higher because we see some stuff back
here that we're involved in
um let's see there
there there so let's at least see if we
can get it to here
overall let me see
yeah overall I'm thinking here I was
looking to get up above this here but
you could have a rejection right here or
somewhere um between this here but
overall I see it getting up above
that just based on going one time FR
out
so pushing that high
now we get up into here we know that
there's a possibility that what it's
it's 10:00 now maybe 10:30 or so let's
see what this
um actually does because this is the new
4our low right here that's been put in
and this is a where the 4 Hour
start started
here so this is a 4our wick down below
and then we move the and this is the
bullish continuation of that 4our Wick
that's in
there so that means that that down move
now this is the 4our candle extending
that momentum up to potentially a 4-Hour
High some kind of
um ah okay yeah that's what I'm seeing
then there's that 4our fractal and I'm
potentially looking for price to get up
above that 4H hour fractal that's right
there so 4our moves have 4our
targets and you do not
fight against that Target until it is
achieved and then that's when price will
look to consolidate and then turn around
the other way so
um it's in this 4H hour fractal and it's
more than likely looking for this 4H
hour high as I mentioned this is a 4
Hour um candle so you're that momentum
that 4our momentum is on your side
leading to a 4our run of something
that's what you have to remember when
you're in 4our moves it's heading to a
4H hour run of something so we know that
this is the 4our POI that is in here
this 4our fractal but I would more or
less be anticipating price to get up
above this tick right up above this and
then drop back within
it or maybe leave behind a wick maybe
leave behind a wick so so that would
be this 10:00 opening push that comes up
and nearest to lunchtime that would mean
that we would be back
here back to wherever we currently
are to leave that Wick there and then
that 2:00 Wick trades up above that 4our
candle and then now looks to trade down
into wherever
it would have came out which is that POI
there so that's how it would look you
know um over the session over the
session
um but so just keep that in
mind so you see this there still running
up to there we would expect that we
would expect some form of a pullback
after we get up above here and that can
just be a little um uh sort of
consolidating there to what maybe dip
into a five minute imbalance or or you
know some higher time frame imbalance
that it might leave behind there and
then you know that first higher time
frame imbalance puts in a new high you
know so it it looks like you know we
have quite the
push um to the top side from this
low and I know everybody's like hey you
know wouldn't it have been better if you
just held all the way yeah that would
have been a banging trade you know that
that have been
amazing but it's not every day that that
you come by that that kind of extension
coming out of there so you got to be
content with you know where you pay
yourself what you get out of the move
for the show back up tomorrow or or
whenever the Market opens back up Sunday
right
I was happy with my plus 3.6R trade then
priced with another 200 points listen we
we were all we were all at least on the
right side right we we were all we were
all on the right side of the market at
least at least that matters
but uh what's up M how you doing uh uh
Dylan K what's up T what's up Chris
what's up how you doing uh hey P baby
what's up what's up morning
morning um bake what's up how you doing
morning morning Sam what's up Franklin
what's up how you doing Lou what's up
how you doing Scott what's up how you
doing oh what's up baby how you doing
Dan what's up man Dan my man Dan what's
up how you doing
um ml is L Series okay cool cool cool
okay and you know I'm going to um do a
market review uh later today about this
uh entry as well but this is It's
self-explanatory you know like come on
we we we know how we trade right we
follow Market structure on the way up
right that's what we we all do that
right that n and meat right so uh you
know when you have this high that breaks
there and you got this low here right
that's that first move there we dip into
it right here right and you see a move
higher right so
now there's that second swing there
right we dip into it
bam trade higher off of it now here's
another one created here right so we dip
into it again and then what trade higher
off of it right then we create another
one there right so you're just literally
following lows or or this is why the
trend line Traders they make they make
more money than everybody else because
they just follow whatever the market is
doing downtrend let's trying to find a
move going down and if it surprised me
and go up okay does the trend line break
now I can find a move going up and we
kind of just over complicate everything
else by you know just trying to be
contrarian there a 4our 4H hour
extension who who GNA be shorten that
from up
here let Dody brag about his
uh his inversion was set up for life I
I'm telling you know he 100% I watch him
develop that from going from being
uncertain about it to to now you know
being very conf confident in calling it
uh Win Lose or Draw I've watch him
develop that so you know it it's
interesting to see that stuff you know
sort of play out um that way and you
have profitable losers cigar delivery
down right to
dodgy uh uh one setup for life on his uh
uh invers inversion going up right so
that's one one strategy there there's
another strategy there right you have
the swing the 50% of the swing that we
were using that that's us you know
utilizing the swing points to be able to
uh trade from them you have
um uh you know this here is what people
would consider the sndr the thing that
sent price up to break this high up
above here so this is price hitting that
um snd responsible as well this is us
tapping to 30% of the snd responsible
there's a lot of stuff going on in here
this is the break of I mean this
mentorship material but it's is mm's you
know like there's there's a ton of stuff
happening inside of this entire Dynamic
here to be able to pay somebody taking a
short heading down pay somebody taking a
long heading up pay somebody taking a
little you know quick scalp um uh uh you
know minor pullback from up above here
you know the there's a ton of stuff
within here and it's all about just
being there when it happens now the the
biggest issue that ends up happening
with people is
that when they get something like this
or or let's even say AO like
this this is what cost
them right
you see how we went up on this Wick we
pushed up on that Wick real sharp
looking like we were trading back into
that direction this is where everybody's
thinking okay price is going to trade
higher then it ends up trading lower
right so after it trades
lower what people end up doing is
grabbing this as a Zone to
use because now
that's a Zone to short right and what
you see is price go right through that
zone but they were looking for a zone
now changing bias to short down and take
out this low here because they said oh
yeah there's tons of liquidity down
these are people that they they know
where the liquidity has but don't don't
know where to put the stop loss it turns
of liquidity down below I don't have
enough money to run run any of that I
can't really say that that's there's
something that's going to happen you
know because of something IM balance
that one here in one minute
but you hit
this right there you have this break
Above This high right here with a wick
right and what you have is
price tap right back into
this Zone here right the imbalance that
broke the high that that's what it
actually hit in traded higher or if you
just take this the 30% of of the uh uh
30% of the Zone 30% of the down move
right close below that's the protected
High trades up above it but that's a
that's a wick right there there are some
times where you're going to get a wick
that will tap back into it and go and
there are other times where you get a
body which one should you use to say
that price is actually flipping to the
upside or flip it to the downside a body
not a wick a body yes the using a body
will cause you to miss out on little
opportunities like this right where you
wanted to wait for the wick you wanted
price to come back and tap you in and
you never got to tap back in the entire
time right you see that you see how
steep this trend line
is where you never got to tap back
in no tap back into no zone or nothing
it's just going going going going going
going going going going going going
going going
going it's just going going going going
and there's no way to get in for
you
right somebody said he exaggerating he
didn't have to do all of that going
somebody WIP in the background
so here we are at at the
4our high that we said we wanted to get
taken it came a lot faster than we
expected right but the 4our
high that that fractal that we wanted to
see taken out right there right so now
here is
where we expect right what do we what do
we usually say in the the the market
reviews I see some people here that are
members of the channel the market
reviews literally tell you guys after
taking at a structural High that's a
structural High to the left even though
it's not a higher high that it's running
it's still a structural high it's the
zone that sent price down that's taking
the high out right here so that is
taking a structural high and that's why
you see this move down right this move
down now now the the cites and the bites
are going to say that it's it's is the
imbalance the ciites and the bites they
can say is is the imbalance is the
inversion that it went back into tapped
into to have all that explanation as to
what exactly that is the support and
resistance guys is going to be like well
it's just retesting that previous
resistance and then you have the Quasi
Moto guys who are just like yeah okay it
went there you traded below went back up
traded and when it went down it came
back to test the other side of that and
then the head and shoulders patter are
going to be like yeah is this the head
and shoulders coming up you have all
these different concepts that are in
there
right all these different
concepts that are present inside of why
this rejection here at the top of this
uh Wick is
happening but no real application of how
to trade
it right when to wait for
it you know how how to anticipate the
move coming from there so when we had
mentioned at least wait for it to take
this High because you're in a 4H hour
bullish momentum so you want to see it
at least strip something on the 4 Hour
there's the high and the entry that's in
there clear as
day was the cell
stop and where did we say we're heading
back into some higher time frame
imbalance that's there
right that's what we're going to expect
price to get back to
whenever it it gets up into this area
and begins to uh consolidate we want to
see it come back into a higher time
frame imbalance and it gets that a
higher time frame imbalance and a higher
time frame imbalance stings it back up
into that previous range that it has now
fallen out
of up above the let me move some of this
stuff
out like that
so the the moment to time of
short would never have been
here right especially with our swing
count as we're heading up right it would
have been being that we notice where we
were in the 4our momentum it would be at
a
4our POI or some sort of 4our
area of significance or something like
that that that's you know there to begin
to look for any of that countering this
move up but the problem is people
counter it every single down candle that
that's here oh it got to be going down
here no it got to be going down here no
it got to be going down here you know
what this Market should be going down
because Joe Biden last night was an
embarrassment to
America and you mean to tell me that
there's no confidence in him at all so
this Market should be going down all of
these biases coming in
here as to why the marget should
dump and it comes back to Asia and pumps
the other way what how how far was that
pump because that was
incredible 235 points the other way
so the very first thing you can you can
credit a move like this to is
understanding where your
4our direction is is headed your
4our
U your 4our momentum what what 4our
candle are you
in are you in a 4H hour candle that's
you know looking to create a dogee are
you in a 4-Hour candle that's
expanding with a
body you know what what kind of 4H hour
candle is it now that's determined by
the 4our POI that it Taps into
right so if the 4 Hour is just moving
with momentum You're Expecting body with
semi you know uh uh uh sized Wicks on
smaller sized Wicks on the sides of them
those are just bodies so it's small
Wicks on each side but when it Taps into
its
POI the kind of 4H hour candle that
you're expecting now is not the same you
know manipulate
upward drop downward and then trade back
in like the regular
ohlc um you know that that we often see
now you're looking
for the either the the
dogee or the flat candle that has a wick
at the bottom of it that runs back the
other
way so if you know the orientation of
that candle where's the open of the flat
candle at the top right what does it
just do dump
and then what happens it closes with the
wick at the bottom and what does the
next candle do pump to the to the the
flat surface that was left up
there those things often happen
in uh London overnight where we have
this Asia dump followed by this hellish
pump in in uh uh New
York so when when we have those things
if you know how the candle closes based
on the POI that it's in then you trade
in the
direction you trade in the direction of
the kind of candle you know price is
forming is it a reversal candle that's
those pin bars morning Stars whatever it
is they want to call it you know the the
well that's getting into bars you know I
really don't want to go you know too
deep into that because you guys still
need to understand structure right but
when you get into understanding the bars
you could predict the entire day based
on the POI that it's in you can know
whether today is going to be a a range
Day based on the POI and based on the
kind of candle that comes out of that
POI all ad doe is is a range and traded
up above trade it down below and came
right back to the center point of it so
now you know the market moves up and and
then it goes down below and then it
comes back to the center of it and you
know to trade either extremes I'm going
trade the high of the dogee then it
drops back down and puts in the low
right oror trade the low of it and it
trades back to the center right so
that's how you know you're in a I
mean let me not go too too far
into into
um you know sort of the the the detail
specific things of of bars candlesticks
but um you come into the market and just
do the same thing every
day and when you come into that and do
the same thing every day you know it
it's it's a glorious
thing it's glorious feeling so this is
the this is the first imbalance right
that's down here right so let me
actually just double check uh what
imbalance that is it's the five minute
imbalance
uh let me
see 12 minute imbalance is
here okay so we're in this fractal right
now 12 minute
fractal this right here I would
anticipate
price to when it looks for this low move
back into that high there so um I'm
still expecting this high up above here
to be taken
out um but a lot of this times it's is
just when you know uh we could hit this
fractal here you see we already hit the
30% and started curling at it we could
hit this fractal here this is 12 minute
fractal and trade back into the high or
the possibility of the low of the
fractal going and then going back for
the high it's just you know whichever
um whichever one that that
uh they choose to do would be all based
on
structure right will be all based on
what we have uh within
here so we know we have this let me move
this
to to the side we know we have this Wick
price ultimately might look for the low
of it so you might get like a little tap
down into here at 30 230 and it could
bring you back up to if it leaves this
Wick at 44 it could bring you back up to
44 um but
we're here and we're still anticipating
this High
here to be taken out
okay
yeah so this that
um uh 50% tap the one to one delivery is
above this high this Wick High here I
thought it would have dropped into here
and then went back to this uh Wick High
22 and then back
to 44 and
but looks like it's responding out of
this POI here this Wick
here e
I don't know if it quite took it let
me oh no I didn't take it yet
so this is back into the wick a second
time
um we have 10:30 here so remember what
we say about 10:30 with 10:30 there's a
possibility of um
depending on the direction that it's
going in um they could be one more high
or one more low after 10:30
so large candle going in you just want
to be mindful of this you're not uh
using something like that remember what
we're ultimately looking for is the
sweep below here right and then the move
back into the ring
there because this is a higher time
frame
imbalance that we're in right here so
just trail that down candle high and
then you'd have some idea of when to go
back into the range
the
momentum looking at
it if it can contines it could be
looking to get back to
this High
here at 47
probably thinking that 55 high too
but I don't know
um mic is super
low uh why the 12 minute that's just
something that I with back testing I saw
for myself it worked and then that's
something that I started to teach
most people who learn from me you'll
hear them using the 12 minute the 144
minute that's you know one of those time
frames that you're going to know yeah
that person you know just uses it from
from this particular concept but it's
just a lot easier to to see that way
it's like a rule of rule of 12 almost
you know um it's 12 5c candles that make
up the one minute time
frame it's 12 one minute candles that
make up the 12 minute time frame it's 12
12 minute candles that make up the 144
minute time frame now you don't you
don't necessarily have to use that you
could use some other variation of of
whatever higher time frame to lower time
frame you like to look at but for me I
know that um I see the clearest with
those time frames frames that's it is is
a a fractal way of of viewing price you
got to think about it so look at this
look at this let me let me just show you
this real
quick
so if I wanted to
see I don't know something in here let's
say in order to take a trade I need it
to see a pullback into an imbalance
before taking a continuation trade right
here right and we have this high that
was taken out right
here I should be able to go to some time
frame and find the imbalance within here
right if I like to take entries off of
those fresh imbalances that that put in
new highs so I don't know exactly oh I
didn't realize we were on a 30 second my
bad
um you know let's go into
something within here there's the one
there we
go so now that same imbalance let me
um just uh move some of this stuff up
here now that same Zone that I used
below
right on the 4our time frame it was an
imbalance so this is tapping
into the first imbalance balance that
puts in a new high right here
right so the 4our time frame showed the
imbalance
there but any other time frame below it
one minute showed snd responsible for
the
break 15 minute uh same thing that's the
responsible for the break with an
imbalance right in the center of
it 12 minute when there's two imbalances
inside of it you want need to second one
another first one that's something
teaching the mentorship five minute you
have a sweep of a zone right up above
and and price Taps into you TR High
there's fractally you go all the way
back there is whatever it is that you
need to see right to take an entry
within you know that that POI that price
is leaving leaving from but you can go
to um you know the the the 4 minute you
can go to the uh I don't know you got
any 11th Hour Traders you you 11th Hour
you know whatever it is look at this
look at this beautiful the 11th Hour
woke up at 500
a.m. tapped into that first imbalance ye
went to go run and put in a new high now
there an 11th Hour up candle that's up
here right right there will beat right
at that time
that we could have Justified a a tap in
there for you know like there's there's
a you can go to whatever time frame go
to I don't
know
uh three day maybe now we're in a
three-day Wick hey whoa look at that
y'all we we ta to a three-day
Wick no wonder there was some heavy
momentum coming out of there you know
you go to you know I don't know two two
weeks maybe
even so this looks like they this looks
like they're going
to um seek to put in a new high maybe
drop back below there this could
actually be a dogee over the next two
weeks up in here up above here the
following two weeks tap into there
another two weeks down maybe hit that
fresh and balance following two weeks
after that go back up putting a new high
up above there you find it on any time
frame the thing you love to trade the
thing you love to be able to execute on
you can find it on any time
frame and trade it but you first have to
understand how price moves
first then you go to the time frame in
which you want to see this particular
thing you know um play
out so look at that bang nice little you
know buy stop right here that would have
ran to this this high at
47 I
was I was thinking more of the 55 but
you know whatever you
know I I just I just suck at this that's
really what it
is seven points seven seven points I was
wrong about seven points
so now you see us digging further into
that imbalance here but but pay
attention to the highs that we have here
so we have that one here right we have
this one here right we have that one
there right they all belong to to uh
lows right there a third low there right
so this is a third thir low digging into
an
imbalance we can move back up into that
direction there and trade out but if we
end up failing to put in that new low
down here you know that this
high is what they're looking
for so it's all about timing you can
time entries going back into the range
perfectly yes you can time entries
trading back into the the previous range
During certain periods of uh
consolidation that you
anticipate we mentioned that we were to
anticipate consolidation
why because we took out something
structural to the
left so if we understand that that we
took out something structural to the
left and we know that consolidation is
getting ready to um occur now we want to
look at the boundaries of our
consolidation the boundaries of our
consolidation is between that higher
time from imbalance that's below right
and then the wick that it left up above
if it's the first Wick there then that's
toilet paper people right inducement
whatever you want to call it the second
Wick up there now that could very well
be sent in the market lower after that
consolidation that happens with the
second High that's put in but whenever
we have that first high after taking out
something to the left and we have this
imbalance below we know that there's
consolidation up here because a higher
time frame dogee occurs up here right
and then the next hour's time frame Taps
into the the uh uh imbalance below right
and then the following hour that that
one hour can move its like you squeeze
its way up but the following hour now is
the candle that pushes out of it so you
have to be able to um you know follow
follow them that way follow
consolidation that way and I think that
um that's something that that could
certainly uh
improve a lot of your your trading or or
just like the the whole fomo
aspect you know we know that there are
times where uh we are early we
understand that so if we understand that
there are times where we are early then
we need to start
trading right we need start trading with
the understanding that we could possibly
be
early so if you could possibly be early
then the size that you're going in with
you need to know is not the proper size
to to be going in with the areas that
you're you're um targeting you need to
know that maybe that's not something you
should be targeting on the initial
entry your initial entry should Target
your confirmation for bullish
momentum right or your confirmation for
bearish momentum so what I mean by that
is if we trade in this Zone
here if we are trading in inside of the
the previous range of this Zone
here
and you see us tap into the zone
from down below here
right this is the
manipulation that happened here this is
the break right of that previous
protected high that we have over there
bam we took it out right there I thought
this was with a oh this is a body
because of the 30 second time frame okay
so this this is with with the body here
we go and trade back into the zone right
here right to Now find that confirmation
to trade
higher so if your entry is here your
target is the confirmation to send us
bullish
because price often times is going to
get to that previous candle's high but
if there's no strong close above it no
body close above it then what you end up
having is uh uh we hit that Target yeah
and then we trade lower like that right
but if this is your Target and then your
other Target what you're thinking about
is potentially here right maybe this
high right here or or maybe even
something within here right if you're in
on this entry you need to know that
price can come back and retest that
entry so
that entry there and that Target there
is a great Target to have now should it
want to trade higher you Trail
below we just changed the color for this
you Trail below these down candle lows
or these down swing lows you're trading
below that below that there as it's
continuing to make its way up below that
swing up there below that one there
below that one there below that one
there until price finally moves you out
of that
position but it has to start here in the
center of the Zone it has to start in in
the zone itself and then that allows you
to manage the problem is some people get
a tap into the Zone here right and
because they don't trust it they see
price get here and now this is where
they want to get involved there but when
price already delivers that one to one
and drops back the other way to now go
and take that low they get caught in
having to risk that whole Zone and eat
that entire risk
versus just using
zones that align with the things that
they are successful with in back testing
so I see my zone I see my flip in the
zone I Target the one to one there
should I want to trade higher there I
would find a re-entry somewhere within
here to potentially go higher there and
then that's where I'm out and that's
where I'm
done right so what did I say we were
going to have I said we were going to
have a tap back into the imbalance right
and then potentially a new high being
put in up
above right so if we have a tap into
that imbalance and a new high being put
in up
above then that means that when that new
high is established up above now I'm
looking to short back
into that range that's there now that's
if price provides me with that
opportunity to trade higher right if
it's not going to trade higher I know
that my opportunity to short I mean
sorry to Long
exist down in these
lows exist down in this Zone that we
have here left behind exist after
potentially some sweep you know stuff
like that I know that's where it
exists and anything within here is still
tied into this being the top of the
range and this over this element over
here being the bottom of the range
within
there so if I was in an entry and had
any internal targets it would just be
because I would be trading
this consolidation that I was
anticipating after this structure high
was taken to the
left and that's how we
have our
nft look at that that's
perfect there we go nft
but none nonetheless nonetheless let's
let's let's bring it in because you know
how you guys get um this the perfecting
now okay okay we we going relax we we
won't
we we won't
uh we won't go too far in today's stream
uh so
um uh
uh if you can get the um uh that
narrative that I just gave entire
narrative that I just gave from the 4
Hour to down to the time frame we're at
to down to why we expecting the range to
down to what we you know Target within
that range to down to you like all of
that stuff in there
um if you truly understand the fractal
nature of price and if you truly have
gone through the
material then you would hear what I just
said and you'd be able to grab it with
with no issue you'd be able to
understand that you'd be able to take
notes and you'd be able to back test
each part right because I I explained
many different parts just now you'd be
able to Gras each
part right each part of what I said
and um I think
that uh that that would help with that
whole um how to determine daily bias
question like you know how to determine
session bias how to you all all of that
stuff you don't need to determine any of
that it's not your business it's not
your business at all to determine you
know what price is going to do for the
day right when you're looking for an
entry it's your business to know where
price is
going when you are looking for your
entry there's the only thing that you're
concerned about that's the only thing
that you are worried about you do not
care where Terminus for the day is it
does not matter to
you so um take that little part that I
just gave youall the little small uh
excerpt there and uh um you know digest
it I think that um it would
be very helpful
um
for for many of you guys uh Trading
so yeah that that was a lot that was a
mouthful
um I'm tired I actually took a little
entry during that the mouthful as well
um but let me
just take it out here I think I'm going
close
here this looks like it may push a up um
[Music]
2011 uh is what I'm closing at but I'm
looking for price to get up to 2115
that's what I was looking
for oh my gosh
don't oh okay
look at that I tell them where my my
target is they just turn the other way
don't worry I'm in at the low
so they'd have to come and be me down
here and that's what they just did be me
thank you thank you
price and that funny soon soon as you
say you
in soon as you say you in but I I still
think we getting getting back up above
that 2011 again um but I want to see
price uh hit that
yeah look at y'all see how they just ran
right back down to get me me out of all
people
me what did I
do I'm maging going for that on 2011
there so yeah that uh
um uh
uh the little breakdown that I gave you
guys of this um that's something that
you you guys should um
100% uh
uh you know write down and and sort of
try to understand from the higher time
frame to the lower time frame anything
that I was explaining just now just has
a lot more to do with the fractal nature
of price and and not anything that's
tied to like any kind of you know Enigma
strategy now um I am coming out with a
10 a.m. model um for for uh some of the
students to use so it's something that
they can definitively and mechanically
use after 10:00 a.m. to um begin to find
that that uh uh you know sort of easy
entry instead of trying to be a part of
the market open move and get absolutely
blitzed like I am at break even here
just crazy they they just they don't
want me to be
great Sam please I don't want to go back
to to to midnight I don't I don't want
to go back to spread Sam please hold the
maret up
Sam hold the maret up
please so yeah yeah
um all right there we go again thank
you I'd wait until
47 really
yeah and then that internal High that's
there that did not make it as a part of
structure right here is what I'm
thinking could be
um Scout
let me see
all right
so we have this here I'm thinking price
is looking to uh come back to this right
here get back into
this Zone up above here so this would be
the um
down candle you're going to see price
close up above to move back in to trade
higher we don't have that yet so we have
nothing uh we do have that
little what time frame is this
okay oh they they here
comes here comes that that uh let's see
I'm going second 12 seconds left I told
y'all about my U favorite candle right
[Music]
oh so this is this is still the target
this is still um what we need to close
up
above but now we're clearly here
all right
let's
sweep right here is the
high this is where you need the
close and I'm trying to figure out if
it's the 30 second has the candle that I
want the one minute doesn't
actually no the oh yeah it does it
does yeah so I'm thinking back to that
uh uh 178
181 uh area over
there I think that's what we could
um be looking going to spring back up to
um I'm going to take a
[Music]
to
170 yeah
170 bet you guys might want to wait for
the close above um 48
yeah 148
we delivered a one to one from the
hourly
Zone Ah that's beautiful um I think
there that hourly higher time frame Zone
you talked about to the left
right yeah that's
nice
um I still don't have a closure yet but
I might be looking to take a long off of
this hasn't gone up above the down
candle yet so you stuck with
nothing yeah I don't
and there's my favorite candle telling
me
that you're getting ready to have
a little move back into this
range so when this candle stops I'm
going take a long right to this high
right here what's that
yeah 29
and being that these are um quite a bit
of swings on the way down um what is
this uh let me see so it's one two three
four five that's the fifth swing
there the fifth swing there and you have
this one to one up here at
178 uh
that's what I'm thinking with this
careful of
that like I see the the momentum heading
down
but you usually
expect you know some sort of retracement
that's about half to
move back into that direction and then
if it wants to head down again then you
have the same type of dip down and then
you assume some sort of retracement back
into when it's moving down in structure
like that so right now the only reason
why I'm even taking along down here is
it has more or less to do with me being
in the lower portion of the zone you
know being at the bottom of the range um
and after the sweep that was in
there so you saw it run out both of
these uh lows inside of there you saw it
tap right into this zone lower and then
a push back into that range and I
usually tell people um Target the 50% of
the imbalance or you can Target the
previous candles high on a uh scalp like
that so if you know
um the momentum that you're heading down
in right and then the momentum that
you're heading back up
in and then the momentum that you're
heading back down in and then the
momentum that you're heading
back up in if you look at it it ends up
looking like this very
[Music]
structured moves even if there's
consolidation below here that's the
thing that a lot of people don't see or
a little consolidation that happened
within here before the drop or a little
consolidation here that happened you
know right there or a little
consolidation is here that happened here
a lot of people see these consolidating
points
and you see a push up above it it goes
down below it a push down below it it
moves back up above it a push back up
above it it goes back down below it a
push down below that consolidation it
goes back up above it so a lot of people
get caught up in
that right not understanding that if you
zoom
out this is
all this all has its its uh purpose
everything within there that essentially
moves it higher then it's there and then
it moves it lower then it's there and
then it trades up above there and then
it's there then it moves back down below
there and then it's there and then it
drops lower and then it's there at the
bottom
right and then drops lower and then
there and then drops lower and then
moves back up like
that so guess what within there there
there there if you can count that you
can time
if you can count that you can trade
it so that's uh
uh my uh
uh you know reasons for sort of what I'm
looking
at and why I trade even in in the way
that I do this entire move down somebody
can take Longs I mean uh uh shorts
heading down and count their swings as
it's heading
down somebody can do that and I can take
a trade at the beginning of every single
swing that reveal feels itself every
single swing that pumps back into the
other direction I can take a a long
with if I know the origination of that
where it's going to happen
right and I know what it's turning
around to
Target I can be a part of that that
entry
expecting Candlestick flip for higher um
possibility a possibility
yeah and that's the thing if it if it
ends up creating imbalances and you know
you have it uh going lower let's say
it's like that if it ends up creating
imbalances on the way down that's
fine trailing these highs right trailing
these down candle Highs are what saved
me from getting into an entry
prematurely when the invalidation would
be behind this
low right
there the invalidation will be right
behind this low so getting into an entry
prematurely it would
just be trailing behind these lows these
down candle lows I mean sorry down
candle highs and you would just need
price to close up above it close up
above that previous
high so I got beat again on that
one I'm still seeing that 129 there it's
just not
um coming to
fruition and I guess maybe my targets
could be just a little
too my initial targets might be just a
little too
um too distant for myself but I think
that that 29
is is
good it's just price is
not giving me
that so you usually what I look for here
is this is a sweep on the lower time
frame right so if I'm looking at that
sweep on the lower time frame and you
now have price trading up above to that
same candle's high that would be a sweep
of that low and a sweep of that high
that occurred so that would be a down
move right that put in an up move it
traded lower below it and then it traded
back up above of it that's what that
down candle closure
is and that's why it's better to wait
for the down candle closure than to
scalp the way that um you know I do with
the initial tap into the Zone most
people may not know what zone they're
they're
um you know essentially trading from or
trusting right now I'm looking for an
entry long within here because we're in
the lower portion of our zone right and
I'm looking for price to get back into
at least that 30% portion and
potentially the high the um the high of
the zone and this is because we've
deeply mitigated the zone now so my risk
can be a lot lower down below here than
me looking for higher prices up above
here my my uh uh uh stop loss isn't as
large in highs as it is in
lows so
um that's the only reason why I'm um
down here even paying attention to any
of this
all
right yeah
so
[Music]
um this is
let's
see so let me do this
instead he said one to one long
delivered yeah it it did so this this
entry let me let me show you guys how I
keep getting
Beed right there would be fine yeah let
me show you guys how I keep getting
Beed so now obviously I told you guys
I'm looking for us to trade into into
that region up above here so you see the
side is a little higher now but this is
still within the same context here right
this is tapping back into this Wick
right and then we trade higher off of
the wick right same thing is here
tapping back into this Wick right and
then we trade higher off of the wick
that was my initial Target stopped out
again at the lows cool trading back into
this Wick right there's that Target
again 129 you see how much is delivering
though is giving me my 10
points my 10 points that that is giving
me my 10
points but that's when the target is too
far away I'm cutting myself short of the
profit that's in here the profit that's
also here and if there's another low The
Profit that goes back into there I'm
cutting myself short by trying to Target
something that price may very well not
be ready to to you know take out
so why not just take the previous
candles High previous candles low you
know why why not just uh shoot for
targets like that Nimble
targets instead and you can quickly pay
yourself get out and and enjoy the rest
of your
day and it doesn't have to be on 10
contracts that whole run up that it made
that was 200 bucks 10 points
already 400 bucks on two
contracts you know but th those are
things that that we you know kind of
deal with as Traders where we measured
this out and we said we wanted to go and
take that right there and we're up a
considerable amount and then what bam it
stops us out and then goes goes the way
that
the we want it or or it could it could
go the other way it could go down again
but bam it stops us out and then goes
goes the way we
want you know um so I I think that um uh
when we're in price actions that are
like this you know in general we get a
lot of that consolidation there remember
what I said I said
that if this is the tap that's in the
zone right and this is the previous High
that's here right that tap that's in the
zone that you're taking the manipulated
tap what you're targeting is whatever
the bullish
confirmation is right if you got in at
the lower portion of that tap so what is
the bullish confirmation the bullish
confirmation
is price trading up above the previous
candle's high and
closing it's the first thing there's not
there's not confirmation that that is
bullish confirmation to go and take out
this high now up above here but that's
the first thing to say it's bullish
confirmation to get involved in a
pullback right get involved in we had
this huge drop that happened from here
right all the way down below here to
about 195 195 points so that move going
back up often times can retrace about
what 30 to 50% of that entire drop like
that right y y'all know that's where
people get the the um you know the the
OT uh stuff that they you see I put on
the FIB wrong the OT
ye you know uh
um entries to to uh short down that's
where they get that stuff up above there
so you know that if if it's designed to
even respect any of those Concepts like
that then it's
it it's designed to move that
way right likewise this is this is the
same thing the same thing down somebody
has you know this here and there's
there's their OT right
here they in their OT entry
here and there are times where they're
right and there are times where they're
not but being able to find moves within
just whatever part of the the algorithm
you're in and localize it to that part
right localize it to that part to take a
quick snap a quick scalp something like
that within there then you
know that's the essence of being able to
come in take a quality move and
go being able to come in take a quality
move and go so we
also pointed out that this is
so if I'm bullish back into this here I
would need to see us close up above this
high at 129 that's why I was targeting
that as the structural high but this
here is the previous candle's high that
we you saw us tap right into the Zone
here and then we go to run that's the
bullish confirmation the previous
candle's high so we trade up above that
previous candle's high right here and we
close right you see
there and we tap right into the 50% of
it right and then what do we do we
deliver a one to one right off of
it extends higher up above that but this
is still holding it
right with the potential Target
of the high here right and then that
that um imbalance that's up above
there so we have this up
move that it's getting re projected out
of uh here right but that's weakening
this move to where price could
potentially take out the high of of
uh the The Zone
itself and that's just the reading this
consolidating bit you know you have a
wick down here
right so you know that in this lower
portion should price stab below these
lows here you know it's little bounce
here that could move you back up into
here you know there there's a ton of
stuff within here that you can read to
be able to take little micros you know
snaps or scalps of a trade that could
result in 10 20 30
points if you were just in the right
position and waiting
right in the right position and waiting
and and you have some idea right of
where pric is
going don't forget
that cuz a lot of people think that they
can trade without knowing where exactly
it's it's going where it's reaching into
now for me I can start up here and say
hey I'm going to count my swings here I
already had the third swing here right
you guys heard me mention that it was it
was um the break of the the low on the
inside here then we had another one here
and we had another one here so we
already had three swings here so these
three swings I'm only considering
countering
moves after that that's my
personal my y'all hear me my personal
plan doesn't have to be yours it's mine
so when we started to drop here that's
where saying I'm looking for a long
somewhere around here guys I'm going to
take a long I'm looking for long
somewhere that's because my rules showed
up right my mechanical rules showed
up for me to start exploring the
possibility of scalping bels in a market
that's moving to the other side now I
anticipated consolidation and that's not
what we got we got a little brief
consolidation within there yes but It
ultimately led to a move back the other
way but back the other way is just
leading me to what the bottom of the
range so if it leads me back the other
way to the bottom of the range what does
it in turn do when I get to that bottom
of the range it leads me back to the
middle of the range or the top of the
range right so where do I consider
looking for Longs there not a a a trick
question Buy Low sell high
right Buy Low sell
High Buy Low sell high
right Buy
Low right
so
that's why I'm down here looking for
that side of the market yeah I might
have called out a couple you know oh you
could get to 129 and then you have 180
there and all these other things that
that's all speculative but when it comes
time to actually take the entry where
are you
entering it's I told you guys you could
listen to earlier in the video I had no
music in this video for a reason you
could fact check my words I said you can
wait until these sweeps that happen
below here and then you could look for a
move with price trading back up above
that's here in this video you go to the
time stamp and find it same way yall
like to find time stamps of people
saying wrong things you can find time
stamps with people saying the right
thing too right so
um that's that's you know what we get
and and I mentioned 129 right but it's
okay if I'm early
it's okay if I'm early looking for that
I know that there are times where I will
be early I told you guys that that
that's something that we all deal with
right that was even over here that was
earlier this morning I said I may
mention to this this example of us being
early we can legit be early before a
actual move back into the other end we
need to be prepared for that that was me
early right there
and then being able to find the re-entry
here to what still go to the same Target
same Target so yeah it traded lower and
and oh my gosh it didn't it didn't go to
the way I said it was going price
doesn't have to immediately do what I'm
saying it's going to
do but as long as I'm aware of what it's
reaching into
now
then I'm able to trade in that direction
of the market why are you longing a
falling Market because ru
rules my rules already told me I could
not take any more shorts doesn't matter
if the market is shorted my rules say
you know
short Markus short you know
short and because that used to be a
handicap for
me right because that used to be a
handicap for me it used to be a handicap
for me that I used to try and short when
the market wasn't ready to Short
youed be a handicap I'm in on this
little Wick here I'm in on this Wick
here I'm in on this Wick here every
single Wick I'm thinking price is
turning around
and because I used to have that
handicap I found a way to get ahead of
it by what just counting my
swings so now the handicap that I have
is actually the the strength it's my A+
setup I face that loss and when I kept
looking at it I said you keep doing this
dumb thing all the
time what is wrong with
you you keep doing this dumb
thing find a way to empower that flaw if
I'm impulsive it needs to be impulsive
in the right
spot if I'm
impulsive if I'm a person that Revenge
trade it needs to be in the right
spot and then I find a way to get in
look for what price is delivering to and
then I make my money from there and I
walk away and go on Twitter and just
laugh joke chat live your life do what
you going to do but you can come in and
do that that particular thing every
single
day every single day you can do that
particular thing
every day waiting on the other side of
what
10:30 waiting on the other side
10:30 and somebody said this is a this
is an hourly Wick up above here with a
10 to1 right here
so somebody mentioned this is an hourly
Wick up above here so look at look at
what ends up this looks like is is
trading through that look at what ends
up
happening so what they end up doing with
this this is a zone right that
price tapped into right here that's the
flip the beginning right here what they
end up doing with this is they can go
here and bring it back up to there tra
away from the structural low and then
taking it run the low there and then go
all the way back up to that Wick that's
thereafter and that's why you're always
waiting for some type of sweep to
find the larger entry right some type of
sweep to find the larger entry you're
always waiting for that and anything
else that's within it is just a little
small
scalp if you're countering it's just a
little small scalp now this is the lower
portion of the range so remember what I
said we could potentially have a 30
point 30 to anywhere from 30 to 90 point
pullback from from you know within this
this um low here right or from whatever
low we were looking to tap into so this
move up ends up being a 47 point
pullback now we said it could it can you
know buy back up a third of the way or
even half of the way but nonetheless we
know that we're looking for a pullback
down below here that equals is greater
than or equal to about 30 to 90 points
to the other
side so now I have within that 30 to 90
point point uh uh you know uh uh
distance
I have to be able to figure out
something within there to pay
me this is not about being right about a
high or low being taken this is not
about being right more than the next
person there ain't about
that I need to find a way to get
involved in what I believe price is
currently doing now
and I find ways and it's always the same
consistent way each and every time the
same consistent way each and every
time you're not gonna do that to me you
better Target filled okay because that's
what I'm talking
about each and every time so I said that
my long comes after the sweep right and
I Look to trade to the
bullish confirmation
so there's my low to the bullish
confirmation
right very quick I was chatting and
compacting saying all these different
things and then I saw on the screen I
saw that Wick go weeps and then move
back in
okay ladies and
gentlemen they they dancing like that in
the 70 what did I tell y'all was my my
entry that would save my life if I had
to
take one entry and I had
to save my life with that
entry oh
baby I'm sorry y'all I'm I'm kind of
like you
know still carrying over with with the
personality that I have in in the in the
group I forgot y'all in the public I got
to behave with
y'all I got to behave with y'all Y very
judgmental out here so you
know but yes okay I'm I'm done I'm done
uh um executing in there um I don't know
this still look like we pushing up to
that 29 but with that kind of momentum
down here looking like that uh again
that that retracement of that the larger
move is
uh what I was talking about so we can
get back here to this 42 but then
careful because that momentum up if it
keeps going it can go back to take out
this high at um not take out the high
but go back to test the
177 yeah and can go back to test that
high up above here CU all that would be
is just trading back into what y'all
one to ones
right and all that would have been was
just you were just early in the Mojo of
the
50% and you see it dug
into that 70 yall know I said that's my
go-to save my life entry and then it
moves back to the 30 here with
potentially delivering the one to one
after which drops us back into
to it like
that so when it's something like that
all you're really looking for is
somewhere to take part in whatever kind
of
Entry you're seeking to take if I'm
looking to take Longs when we have that
extension up my business I already told
you guys is after the high is taken or
when price drops back into the range
that's it that's my entire TR plan and I
cannot trade utilizing anything else
other than
that so I need my sweep right higher
time frame sweep too and then now I'm
going to trade with whatever price has
established
already and when you trade with them
what price is established already it's a
lot easier than trying to guess what
price is going to
establish right trying to guess what
price is going to establish you don't
want to be the person doing
that so all up here I said that first in
Balance they could put in a new high
blah blah blah blah the 12 minute
imbalance all that is up there yeah all
of that is
there but when it comes time to actually
making the decision it's not being made
because that is there it's being made
because my rules have lined up so in
order for me to hold an entry long I
would have had had to have a flip right
cuzz I know the first tap is a
scalp that break structure that's why I
say that first flip is fake right the
second one usually double bottoms and
then trades out of there which entry are
you in are you in the first tap or are
you in the second tap and that begins to
you know alleviate some of those issues
that people have with just being a
little too early you're trying to manage
the stop loss of the first entry it's
the first entry if you try to manage the
stop loss of it you're likely to get
stopped out and price go way that you
were
anticipating so it's either set behind
the invalidated idea right that's where
your stop loss is or trade within the
understanding that first tap second tap
is is an actual thing
right
um Dave thinking he owns the X in future
space no I own me actually and I own the
level of discipline that I have and um I
uh make sure that I'm uh very uh uh
expressive about it so many of you guys
come in and get upset with my confidence
and I'm just confident in my ability to
follow my rules I'm not confident in in
being able to call whether price is
going to be you know in in 15,000 at at
you know quarter three of of 20 25 I'm
I'm not that's not me but I'm confident
in my ability to follow my own rules and
do the same thing each and every day and
be accountable to if I said that this is
what I'm waiting for I am going to wait
for it and I cannot deviate from that
and if I come into the market with that
mindset each and every day and have that
discipline I'm going to have that
confidence when I talk I walk it like I
talk it and I'm going talk it like I
walk it that's that's the way that I do
things so I apologize if that if that
upsets you uh Mr James yames over there
I apologize if that upsets you but um
you know go check out the playlist watch
it uh 10 times if you will and it might
uh improve your
circumstances uh so um appreciate you
guys for uh uh you know uh coming out um
let me just throw on a banger I want to
listen to a song with y'all uh to get
the negative Spirit out of the chat
right
this Lear me
ize I sing you to sleep do do you like
my
L let you treat your sadness with a
smile you can't have what's next till
you hang with it for a while this is
house come your Sunday
Best this is house
[Music]
arest I learned how to measure before I
knew what was size I to sleep do you
like
my with
smile
while come
suay this is house
this
[Music]
is all right y'all all right all right
so
[Music]
I help sweet made myself
a this won't last forever treat your
sadness with a smile we can have what's
next till we hang inside for a while
this is how is
[Music]
stay all right guys I appreciate you
guys hey profitable losers in the
building I'mma get on out of here I'll
catch up with you guys soon Jared I'mma
watch your stream in a few I hear a lot
about you but I'll see you guys soon all
right catch up with y'all peace
[Music]
out this is how
this is how
[Music]
oh I you