e
[Music]
there something about
you makes me want to
reti want to feel something
true Can You Feel
My I'm a stranger to
the not too late to
re tell me what you I do
want you to take me
[Music]
higher take me
higher
yeah you to take me
higher take me
[Music]
higher
oh hey yeah
[Music]
take me
higher
w
there's something about
you all
[Music]
right y want me to turn up the
music not too late to
rewi tell me what should I do
want you to take me
higher take me
[Music]
higher
yeah look where we are
now how
see we our
heart to fall some
Rel I don't want to calm
down I just want to
be with nobody
else I just
[Music]
want
o take me
high take me
high take it
[Music]
high
all right all
right what's up y'all more on him on
him so what's up y'all
um
I'm doing this uh stream here uh to be
very uh
concise about the
difference in all
Concepts
um again except
bookmap because bookmap doesn't
work so
um uh this drawing you here you you see
here
um you know we uh knew that it would
sort of work out this way one because of
what we often you know uh trade with but
two um because of noticing things that
go alongside the things that we
trade so
um the very
first uh thing I want to address is that
I I am
um I was watching this uh African guy I
I don't know what his name is no idea
who he is um I can't even remember the
video um I'll probably try to find the
video and post it to uh the group as
well as
um uh Twitter as well I was watching
this African guy and he said that he was
teaching I ICT
Concepts Made Simple ICT Concepts Made
Simple hey Mikey what's up what's up
baby what's up hey I want to tell you
your boy Tyler is soft uh I don't really
take recommendations of people who ask
me to open my group and make exceptions
for people and um you know unfortunately
I broke my rules and did it again but
your boy Tyler's a softy I just need to
let you know that um so
um he was
explaining ICT Concepts right and he
mentioned how it was a simplifying
version of it and you know whenever you
see those those
um
uh whenever you see those uh uh videos
you automatically think clickbait scam
you know all of the other stuff but what
I tend to do is spend my Saturdays
watching the the week that has passed in
review so I watch all of the streamers I
look at just everything everything that
that you know has occurred um throughout
the week even on the different pairs and
you know so I clicked on this one guy's
video he was showing ict's Concepts on
binary
options um African guy
named you mean St Kish TCM he's not
African he's Jamaican so uh get it right
um I was watching him
and he was showing on binary options he
was
showing uh what I saw as Market
structure on the way down right like
this
right and he was on the lower time
frames doing that so let me
um just make this look a a little better
so my OCD doesn't you
know so what he
said what he said
was as we
see price actually let let me uh let me
just make this
here
something like
that maybe like that yeah that's
fine so let's call
this a high
here
come on let's call
this an old high right here right at
that red
line what he was
explaining
was that when price took out that old
high and it traded to this low right
here he said each time
and this is this is far better than any
of the ICT um you know streamers or or
teachers or whoever it is that has ever
explained it I just learned today from a
couple ICT Charter students we got quite
a bit of them in in the group um that
this is something that ICT has taught
and explained many times
um but you know for us it's it's Market
structure right right break below the
old low
you put in a high you put in a high and
low again high and low again right and
we count 1 2 3 4 and then we up and see
you know price reversed on you know four
to six and trade high right so that's
that's us that's in there we don't
really have to consider that because we
teach that on the channel already so
what he mentioned was every time you see
a low taken like this he talked about
price he mentioned
rebalancing to a fair value Gap so you
have
this low into this high that took out
the inducement after a old high was
taken right and it's essentially going
down to the cell side right so he talked
about it rebalancing
into an
fvg IT trades below old low goes back
into the
fvg so the same thing happens again
trades below the old
low goes back into an fvg
right ra below the old low back into FG
paid back to from WG right we we all we
all understand that especially some of
you guys that have uh come
from ICT
Concepts and then bam we hit cell
sign let me just put that
there so for us wew you know previous
range previous range previous range
previous range you know we don't have to
go over
that
but when he explained this he was doing
it live on something that people Call a
scam binary
options which is not a scam you just
don't know how to trade
it um and that that's for most things
that you would even call a scam you CME
manipulation well it's just that you
don't know how to trade it um so it's
taking old lows rebalancing into fbgs
right so in terms of Market structure
it's a series of highs and
lows or or uh um lower highs and lower
lows heading down
right
so with that understanding of knowing
that price does this and with us not
needing to use ICT Concepts we don't use
it at all we don't care about fugs none
of that we we already got past that
stuff we don't even use imbalances we
don't look at them we don't even want to
see them
but what the understanding of this is
is that this
is
keeping structure intact right
until we take out the old low right and
then you see a move going back into that
range but what happens
here often times when we take out that
old low y'all remember y you remember
what I teach we end up getting
accumulation right
so we see the
accumulation occur which drives us down
into the manipulation and then you see a
distribution coming out this often times
is what people are getting cooked up in
trying to trade that with no knowledge
of how to trade it because it's entirely
tradeable but you just don't have the
knowledge to trade it so when we get
into that low and we begin to
consolidate and we manipulate lower and
trade higher
what did he end up calling that there's
another portion of his Concepts right
where they call it
the
accumulation the manipulation trust me I
do not care what color these boxes are
supposed to be I don't trade
ICT and a distribution right and that
distribution you could
anticipate
running the old high up above right
going back to run by side and taking
out what they
call low resistance liquidity run all
that other you know Jazz that they put
in there let me just move some of this
stuff so it doesn't look as
messy than let me make sure I don't
delete
everything so the thing
that a lot of uh
um you know people do not understand
and is that oh I forgot I forgot I got I
got a you know oh fvg you know OMG and
then then train highight
right the thing that a lot of people do
not pay attention to within this
particular construct here is
one when we're trending versus when
we're ranging right two different
environments this can happen on the 4H
hour time frame this can be 4H hour
highs and lows that we have have here
right four hour highs and lows this
could be on the one minute be one minute
highs and lows this could be on the
weekly weekly highs and
lows doesn't matter what time frame it's
on it matters about what's occurring so
what we end up having is this
accumulation and on days where we have
accumulation this is where a lot of
people getting cooked up oh it's SE can
destroy you know don't don't trade it
it's garbage PA because you saw some
little little tiny imbalance open up
inside of here and that tiny imbalance
you were supposed to be able to take
that imbalance and then begin the move
higher and then you shift it to break
even and you watch it go lower and then
you end up taking an imbalance inside of
here and you wanted to go down to sell
side and end up trading up above into
into you know your your stop loss there
and then you saw it trade higher and
then you wanted to go into your OT here
and you end up getting oted back back
below because you thought it was
supposed to trade higher there that's
the days where you're creating this
understanding or or or this
idea
that price is supposed to go higher or
it's supposed to go lower we're bullish
no we're bearish no we're bullish no we
bearish nowh bullish nowh bearish nowh
bullish nowh bearish back and
forth hop skipping and jumping in your
bias like like Joey G powerful Joe G or
whatever you call weak weak sauce Jo G
Mighty Joe Young whatever you want to
call them you you you just flipping your
bias oh you got to know when to change
the bias no that sounds like
buffoonery you need to understand what
price is doing and when it is doing it
and how it looks so we have this right
now one thing that the ICT Traders
love to do is trash other
Concepts trash them the only concept i
trash is book map that's it nothing else
but they love to trash other Concepts so
here goes the other Concepts getting
thrown into the
mix now you have the support and
resistance
guys who are
saying well it's just
repackaged resistance turn support you
know they they in here and and they back
up
here and it's just going to the next
level of resistance after it finds the
support and the ICT Traders
go well when we take out this old high
up above right take out that old
high we're looking for price to
rebalance back into an fug that could be
a form of a breaker to the left
and price higher
right and the the support and resistance
guys saying well it's just a break above
the resistance and then it turn into
support and then and it's going for the
other it's going for the other level of
and guess
what the guys that want to be right
about all of this and all of that and
all of that and all of that and all of
that and all of that and all of that and
all of that and all of that they make no
money over complicating it zero
dollar because you have to wait for the
8:30 Kill Zone within the orbital
construct of the vertex and then after
it has formed then you should be
targeting with the smallest stop
possible and you getting stopped out
stopped out stopped out stopped out
stopped out then you flip your bias and
now you getting stop out stop out stop
out stop out stop
out right
St down a little
more and now you went and got a little
bit of profit within
there and you showing on Twitter how you
call a whole move
up you caught the whole thing yeah oh I
forgot my my bad wait wait I forgot we
we forgot how could we
forget how could we we got to we got to
leave a purple line no no no maybe maybe
Brown we we got to put a Brown Line
there we forgot all about that cuz we
have the toilet soup that's down below
here that act
like they reinvented the whole market
and now it unlocks the market We we
forgot about that toilet soup there you
got below here so from toilet soup to
toilet soup oh take take profit at the
50% of the range because it could
reprise higher and they see toilet soup
in here back to go higher you got all of
these different things in here you got
the channel
traders who the channel Traders are
saying yeah well pric is just moving
into a channel and then it breaks out of
the extreme of the channel and then it
goes back up to take out the high of the
channel there you got the people who who
are trading these let me change change
up some of the colors here you got the
people who are who are trading these
these wedge patterns triangle patterns
you know all these different things let
me let me just get them in there I want
to get everybody in
there trading that that pattern there
the the the formation of it the break
and retest of it you got the trend line
guys in here you know they they in there
too you know let let me let me make a
spot for them because you shout out to
the trend line
guys I know it's tough trying to time
thatp
so get the trend line guys in the green
break up above the trend line it's a
false break all right it was a false
break guys false break the next one is
good next one they get it fine they took
two entries lost on the first one got
the second
one so you have everybody in this
Dynamic
here
arguing and saying who is right and who
is
not and the person that's that's that's
you know worth listening to right it's
not the person that knows all of this or
knows the the the ICT part of it or
knows the trend line part of it or knows
the triangle pattern part of it or knows
the S support and resistance part of it
or knows the gtfx zones part of it or
whatever it is that's not the person you
listen
to the person you listen to is the
person being able to time when to get in
and extract oh my goodness I I forgot
wait hold up I forgot
somebody I forgot somebody in
here hold up I cannot be
disrespectful we have DJI with his
inverse fair value G we we we can't we
can't forget
him he's he's in there as
well but all of these things
[Applause]
occurring and people are on social media
arguing
about what is the correct way that the
market actually moves when you could
make money in all of these ways here
every single way possible you got you
even got uh uh Market maker sell model
into Market maker B model all that other
stuff in there you have everything
here
and everybody knows the
Encyclopedia of every single concept
here that
exist and cannot pull a single dollar
out of the
market because what no matter what it is
oh my gosh hold up wait wait
wait hold on wait I
forgot I forgot the the
the the OT games my
bad can't forget about
them and
then let's say this is uh
uh let's say this is uh
um just make it red a brighter Hue of
red because my man profitable losers in
there can't forget about
that all of these different things are
here all of these different things are
here and the market moves in every
single way possible in here right every
single concept we watch occurring here
the market does
it Market does it and that's with and
without
time with and
time with and without time it does
this
so when the market Moves In This
fashion there's plenty of people who
have the opportunity to make
money utilizing any part of these
Concepts that they choose you can put
Elliot wave in there you can put wank
off in there you can put Gan theory in
there you can put the the the uh uh soup
Traders the the turtle sorry not the
soup Traders we already got them toilet
soup do you can put the the the turtle
traders in there you know during that
time you can put the market structure
traders in there you can put any Trader
you want in this
Dynamic and they all have the
opportunity to make
money and the people who know the ins
and outs of every single bit of
this can walk away with
nothing can walk away not being able to
take a single dollar out of the market
why because they've
mastered these Concepts and the way they
look in
hindsight but as it's occurring
they have not
mastered
themselves they sell low and they buy
high they remove their
stoploss they they are
greedy they want to be right about
what's
occurring rather than making
money and they come on Twitter and they
attack
everybody for what they know is
occurring and it's this and it's that
and look at him he was wrong and he the
loudest people in there make zero
do and that's why they have all that
time to just be out
there clacking their
mouth
Zer while all of it is occurring ICT
Concepts work DTF effect Concepts
work toilet soup Concepts work after
you've been stopped out 500 times the
SMC Concepts work do what whatever it is
that's there support and resistance
Works Market structure
works all of it every bit of it and for
the ones I hav't even name they all work
but guess who doesn't
work
you
you are the
one that doesn't
work you can't master
yourself you can't see your setup take
your setup exit the market
profitably and show back up the next day
to do it
again why because you need the Instagram
worthy shot
you need to be right
about where it's going when this is a
market that's not even designed for
[Music]
your wealth
status I'm not going to call you
broke the status of wealth you have not
even designed for
you but y'all get in and when yall start
to find ways to to you know engage with
price the greed takes
over the selfishness takes
over and you walk away with
nothing nothing at
all you do well in the AM you become a
philanthropist in the
PM and all you do out there is argue and
scream and yell and talk about what
doesn't work and who was wrong with this
and who's a scammer that you know who's
scamming you you are scamming your
future you out there yelling on Twitter
acting like you got it all
together knowing that you want to claim
public success right but you are behind
the scenes
failure and you know it deep down inside
and it's easier just to project it on to
other people rather than get yourself
together if you got to go to therapy go
if you got to go to church go wherever
it is you have to go to fix yourself and
fix your life so you can get involved in
this because all of it is out there
trust me every course has been
leaked every course has been
leaked hey you still get margin cold
baby still getting
cooked with every course in the world
out
there it's not the material it's not the
concepts you can pick one in here and be
successful with it I was successful with
trend line
trading that was my first concept and
profitability trend line
trading all the people giving T trades
hell cuz she trendline trading and she
showed up with the 1099 B from her
broker and you ain't hear nothing ever
since trendline trading could be
profitable but it's
you that's who it
is it's you it's
you so you got to get yourself
together get off social
media go and back test until you can't
unsee
it some people be like yeah you you
can't unsee it so how do you see it and
still get your stop loss ran how how do
you see it and still get cooked you know
where all the liquidity is you don't
know where to put your stop
loss something is
wrong
so that's just letting y'all know
that it's not any of the concepts that's
out there it's not the mentorship it's
not the
teacher it's your ability to create a
plan and follow it and you blame
everything and everyone else but you
take accountability for it
you trading every new thing you see oh
my gosh he took that entry and made
money on it I'mma take it the next time
I see it what kind of foolishness is
that chasing
everything but your actual
plan you got to do something about
that cuz soon enough life is going to
Margin Call you
and what would you have done with all of
that time you
had just yelling and screaming at other
people telling other people what they
were and what they wasn't until life
squeezed you and now you over here
having suicidal
ideations I just wish I wasn't living
anymore because you lack purpose and why
do you lack purpose because you can't
even
follow or complete whatever it is you
set out to do you have to keep jumping
from thing to thing to thing until life
catches up to you it catches up to
everybody you know how many 50 year olds
I know working as a cashier at
7-Eleven and all they have to show for
their life is pictures of when times
were
good while they argue about the way
things are now now and how the young the
young people don't know what they got
they don't they are so
ungrateful when it's them okay yeah we
don't know what we got right it was
harder for you right now it's easier for
us that you can't take part in that wine
you stuck
there but blaming the young
people
that will be your life in a few
years if you don't get it
right
so me take this away that that's that's
just about all all the concepts that's
there and why y'all shouldn't be arguing
especially with people who make money
when you
don't
right so what do we have
here what do we have here
we have this low oh boy that
oh let me get that up
SC we have this low and this
high but in terms of
structure we get here to there right
this low we this High We traded below
broke structure right Dave teach is in
here
my look no hands first tap break
structure downside second tap double top
short right that's
there support and resistance guys for
there
right the
accumulation into the
manipulation
right into the
distribution right that's
there
right taking out an old high To the Left
Right rebalancing into a one hour fvg
and trading higher that's there right
right the FIB Traders that's there they
the 61.8 golders though spe we on the
menu heading out right right
DTF X Traders we down in here too trade
above the oh high back to the previous
race it is all
there but you know it's not that oh hold
on hold on wait wait my
bad the the pattern Traders whatever
they call this the
the the uh uh the scone pan I don't know
whatever what want to call it I don't
know they switch it every now again the
trend line
guys break above the trend
line
retest everybody's
there but you're still trying to figure
out
Enigma what concept is the Holy Grail
what is it that I need to
use that's consistent every day it's you
that's supposed to be consistent every
day it's you that's supposed to wait for
that plan to show
up it's you it's
you it's all
there great day in the morning it's all
there but
you
Z for
you forgot the little toilet soup they
down there too tap through there and
then
higher and the little DTF X you know
down here
50% the down move you see his trade up
above
there they call like the inart Zone what
what is it again m
m something like that
some guy infatuated with my Concepts and
just re renaming them is that ad to the
demand
beow is there everything is
there but
you you had to be a part of this candle
that you believed was going down because
Joe Biden is an embarrassment to the
country and then the the sell sign
boys oh they placed that equal load
there they placed that equal
load to run it manipulated to something
lower and that in that trade so we want
Target the equal low at the Kill Zone
and then it go from the Kill Zone to
kill
me take everything from me
and again my man profitable loses in
here but you guys can go and and and
learn his stuff on his own I made a
promise that I would not teach his
things you going learn from the man
himself all in there but
you yeah you you could you could make
the case for that ell way W off all that
other yeah of
course you can make the case for that
the spring retest of the spring whatever
you want you can make the case for all
of
that somebody else took a short out of
the 50% of the imbalance over
here and they got a short for not
imbalance going going into that
direction
there and they their reasoning was
taking this low rebalancing to an fug
right taking this High rebalancing into
FG
below all of it is
there
again but
you so time to make some
changes trying to do something
differently pick a concept stick to
it pick a concept stick to
it I don't tell people you have to trade
my concept and and not
icts if you're going to trade ICT stick
to
it stick to it don't try to throw
everything in the pot like it's
gumbo yeah just a little bit of that and
a little bit of this and we'll throw a
little vwap on that and then we going to
get the EMA for 2069 and then we going
no
one thing and one thing alone and stick
to it because the market does it every
day every day every day every day every
day every day every day the market does
it
each and
[Music]
every
dang can't hear a word you
say I'm talking loud not saying
much but
how
[Music]
we down but it
up I'm
going nothing to
lose far away far away bre sh you take
your far away far
away down but I fall I am
tit you show me down but I W fall I am
[Music]
[Applause]
tit
[Music]
you guys get my
point hey Sean beautiful thank you for
that I think you're the first Super Chat
on the
channel that's what it say here let's
celebrate the first Super on the live
stream hey super Shan super
Shan
[Music]
but do one thing right and I'm
going nothing to lose far away far away
bre the sh you take your rain fire away
fire
away down but I fall I am tit
you show me down but I won't fall I
[Applause]
[Music]
am
all right all right that's that's enough
with the noise there there
enough that's enough with the noise so
it's it's this is just showing you guys
you know that that it's it's all here
you know y'all y'all call ICT a scammer
y'all say all these things about so many
other people and it has nothing to do
with
them whether ICT is actually a scam or
not not going to make you any money how
did you get paid for your investigative
journalism zero nothing
not a
dollar you don't know where to put your
stop loss but you know Act is a scammer
okay so uh um that's that's just you
know something that I felt like I should
come out and say today's my day off you
know I got today and tomorrow off but
I'm not streaming tomorrow so I you know
came out just to
um you know put some things into
perspective for you I did it for the
group you know I was talking with um uh
the premium tier earlier today about
these same things and it's it's the same
thing with you know
um anybody else that I would I would
give any advice to I'm not telling you
guys to ditch anybody else's Concepts
I'm saying find the one that resonates
with your personality find the one that
resonates with your circumstance
some people may not be able to trade to
one minute because they only have a
limited time at work so go up a time
frame you know like there there are so
many things that that you can do to
change your circumstances little by
little little by little
matters because when you're moving
things little by little it it builds and
Blossoms
into something
larger something larger than
that house is it starts with with
what digging the
ground you got to take that shovel and
and dig that first part of the dirt
out it starts with cleaning it out right
clearing it out right they don't just
put it on top of
a a flat surface with no
foundation so the very first part of
found of building a foundation is
what cleaning you out that means that
undisciplined nature you have we all
have it we all deal with it I deal with
fomo at times too as much as I love to
call myself oh I'm the the TR this as
much as y'all see the the the win rate
that I have and all these different
things that that you know the students
are doing and stuff I still deal with
fomo as well I tell yall this Dave
teachers and then there's DJ
Dave DJ Dave is a wild
guy when I feel him coming on I'm that's
when I'm done that's when I'm closing it
up close up shop
nope Dr Jackal and and and Hy is is
about to show up I'm never in the same
room as him DJ Dave but anytime I allow
him to take over the minute I look
up I can't even recognize what
occurred who did
this who was responsible for this that
was that other side that I have to
continue to keep down by what following
my
rules following my rules the rules that
are in my trading plan and if I don't
have a trading plan
[Music]
then
yeah that's one of the biggest issues
that people
have when you don't have a trading plan
that's how you get
cooked you need a
plan and if that plan doesn't
work or it doesn't work as much as you
like it to doesn't show enough
opportunities then find some
else that gives more opportunities some
models give more opportunities than
others that's the truth of the
matter some models give far more
opportunities than others
do and once you start to understand that
and recognize that
then you're on the way to refining a
plan or creating a plan
that can change things for you but it's
never going to be about the mentor the
person that's teaching
you the person can teach it until they
tongue turn
blue they could say every single word
10,000 times to
you and none of that will have any
benefit if you don't put in the time if
you don't put in the work towards
it
so I hope you guys enjoyed this
uh uh earlier segment of of
trading and
um um I hope you guys rewatch this I
think this is very important you know to
this this is psychology this is trading
psychology trading psychology is not go
for a cold
plunge meditate before you get into your
entry
trade and psychology is Define rules and
follow it and if following it causes you
to lose more than you
win create better
rules but if you're not following the
rules that are in your trading plan you
can never say a particular concept
doesn't
work you can never say
that
you can never say something does not
work if you won't even put in the time
for
it you tried it out a couple of times
and it worked a little bit and then
other times it didn't and now you just
gave up on it that's you that's not the
concept that's
you it's
you um Dave can you elaborate more on a
trading plan what entails it just want
some insight I have heard plan many
times but I don't understand what it is
exactly well it sounds like you have no
strategy because a trading plan is
within whatever strategy you've created
from whatever Concepts you
use that's that's what a trading plan
is so for the guys who trade
support and
resistance let's say they were going to
take something like this
right their concept is if we break up
above here and close and retest on it
right they'll be taking that entry that
way but if we break up above here and we
close below here they'll be taking the
retest to go lower that is
their trading plan according to what
occurs
here according to the strategy or the
concept that they follow so for you to
have no plan at all you don't even have
a
strategy you need the concepts back
tested along with how it works out the
win rate if you follow it mechanically
you need that first and then you need to
develop rules around it so oh there are
times where I see it break above here
but it's it's with a wick instead of
giving a body so I'm not going to take
one until they give a body above
there I'm not going to take one until
you see how Tor trades talked about
having the the trend line my rules are
this what you said my rules are three
touches to the trend line there three
touches that's you hear I say that in
every video three touches to those are
rules now I don't trade trend lines and
and that's what I used to trade and I no
longer use them because I have a more
refined way of engaging in the market
but even those have rules so you need a
strategy
first you need to learn a certain set of
Concepts that happen over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over
again Dave are you going to mention M
effect the creative the concepts you
using or you waiting to get cheated on
after buying a
batch I I don't even know what you're
saying but um men of X created supply
and demand the only thing I learned from
M of X was uh uh
wof which that's in the bio or the
description of my course here on YouTube
credited to
him so if you want to look at the other
things I learned go and look at Pips of
Persia who men effect effects also
learned from and with men effect the
same guy his whim rate is a
30% when I joined his group for one
month I said there's no way my kids need
to eat 30% of the time so unfortunately
I cannot follow this one month and one
month
alone but that makes it his content
right right and just invalidates
everything else and makes it his right
foolish
people so you know with with uh
uh with with little things you know like
like your trading plan you have to be
sure that it's rooted in Concepts that
you see work out more times than they
don't more times than they do
not so a 30% wiim rate
terrible that's not something that's
going to change your life that's not
something that's going to feed your
family especially if you need to be a
scalper because you're not provided with
the opportunity of being able to take
one trade from a weekly time frame see
that through you don't have enough money
to swing trade that's where big money is
Swing trading not in is scalping
scalping is the fastest way to
wealth the fastest way to wealth is to
scalp so if you need to be a scalper
anything below a 50% win rate will take
away from your mental Capital it will
destroy your mental
Capital
anything below a 50% win rate will
destroy your mental
capital and because of that you have to
find Concepts you have to find
strategies that work far more than 50%
of the
time far more than 50% of the
time
so um with that trade plan question you
actually need to do more
learning and that's the only way that
that you're going to have a plan that
you
know that uh works for you nothing else
is going to work for
you um I'm sure lots of people have
knowledge on the market for me been
searching for a mentor trading Guru to
learn from for two and a half years no
one has come close to Dave teachings hey
hey but I mean you you can find any
teachers that are out there that that
are amazing in in in their own right you
just have to make sure that the stuff
that they teach they actually trade it I
don't teach ICT because I don't trade
ICT I don't teach W off because I don't
trade W off I don't teach Elliot wave
because I don't trade Elliot wave you
get what I'm
saying so if I teach you that price
takes a high trades back into the
previous range and trades higher or
price price takes a low trades back into
the prev previous range and trades lower
if I'm T if I'm saying take a oneto one
from a Zone it's because I am using it
to make
money I will not ever teach you anything
that I don't use myself that's called
unqualified teaching how can I teach you
something I have no experience with how
can I teach you something I do not use
every day but expect you to benefit
from I
can't you
can't so make sure the person that you
are learning
from right person that you're learning
from they're also trading what they
teach that's why I point out people like
dodgy I point out people like profitable
loser I point out people like like uh uh
Pepe I point out people like stoic stoic
takes a portion of what I
teach and sees it in his own way and
uses it his own way some of his entries
are not the same entries I
take Charles look at the way he trades I
don't trade the way Charles trades but
he trades within what I've taught and he
utilizes it in his own
way so everybody's going to learn
something from somebody and be able to
tweak
it and be able to change it and see it
every day and be able to depend on it on
their own without the other person the
whole point of learning is to stabilize
your approach to what you see in the
market and then take what you see in the
market right and find a way to get
involved with it some of y'all want to
see ICT entries but he already showed so
many things that you can take to trade
with he already showed so many different
you know styles of price action that you
can read yourself
right invine entries with
it so it's not up to him to show every
single entry it's not up to dodgy to
show every single entry he would take
it's not up to him to confirm that you
should take an entry it's up to you to
learn what it is that they do how it is
that they see the market and then
develop your own sight for
it that's what you got to do develop
your own sight for
it and that's literally what I teach
other people just do
that just do
that and that's the fastest way to
become profitable developing your own
Edge in the market
Market your own
Edge so
um I hope that that uh answers the the
question for
you uh should we be paper trading or
just read and price or both um I feel
like I'm left behind with the
group uh and without being able to
finish the playlist uh let me see feel
even more lost any recommendations so
if if I teach you structure as the first
thing that you need to
learn then you need to back test the
hell out of structure and it needs to be
the only thing that you are taking an
entry on is structure you're going to
see times where it does not hold you're
going to see times where it does hold
that's going to add to your experience
of when to use it and when not to use it
but you need to back test the hell out
of
that and then when I go into orderflow
and
narrative then now use orderflow and
narrative and back test the hell out of
that and then when I go into teaching
you about zones now you need to back
test zones and become proficient in
utilizing
zones and then when I go into you so you
you kind of get what I'm saying you move
from one thing to the next thing to the
next thing to the next thing to the next
thing to the next thing you don't try to
throw it all together because that's how
you run yourself
crazy you never try to throw it all
together you have to get good with one
thing and move to the next get good with
one thing move to the next get good with
one thing move to the next and soon
enough it all comes together and now
you're able to see the ones that align
with the
others and what's premium and what's not
what's your A+ setup and what's a setup
that you always see
fail so what did I tell you guys I said
to Trail your highs and lows right I
said to count your swings
right so that means if you're counting
your swings four to six swings in price
reverses right so that means by the time
we get to the fourth swing you're no
longer continuation
trading now you're stepping aside to see
okay he said for six swings in price
reverse let me step
out and watch to see what what it's
going to
do will it actually
reverse
or does it
continue that's one thing to
follow County of swings is equivalent to
trailing and highs and lows now you just
know how many highs and lows get
created before you begin to anticipate
price
reversing but you also know when to stay
out of continuation
trading so those those little things you
you sort of want to add to you don't
have to know all the stuff that that's
there you have to trade every single
concept that's that's
taught get good with one thing and move
to the next thing that's how you
refine absorb what is useful discard
what is not yes yes that's exactly it oh
you quot Bruce Lee you quot Bruce Lee
yeah that's exactly
it because you need to see it for
yourself no one else can do this for you
you need to see it for
yourself and that's how I approach every
day with trading that's how I approach
every day with you know talk about every
day is a profitable day every day is you
know trading day is a blessing to be on
the right side of the market every day
why am I saying the right side of the
market because all I'm doing is
following
structure most times structure will
remain
intact and the times where you can't
understand structure you need to know
that you're in a
Range if you have a high put
in and you put in a low and then you put
in another high after right let me show
you guys
this if you you have a high put in and
you put in a low and then you put in
another high after and you trade down to
here right and it fails to put in
another low and it goes back up here
right and it looks like it's going to
head back down that way and then it goes
back up here and it goes back down to
here and then back here and then back
there and then back there you need to
understand where your highs and lows are
where are your last highs and lows well
there's a low here there's a high here
so
this and this is the last high and low
that we have if we have not put in a new
high neither have we put in a new low
we're in a Range we're
accumulating and you need to understand
that within accumulation price can come
out of any side of accumulation price
can dip below and then trade back up
above or price can trade up above and
then dip back
below but you need to understand when
you're in accumulation versus when when
you're in a trending
environment and it the the dead giveaway
is when we have the high and the low
that puts in a new high and we failed to
put in a new high or a new low you're in
a
Range so if that part begins to get a
little more difficult for you then you
need to know that that's where I step
out of the market and I wait until it's
clear for
me wait until it's clear for
me but some of you guys try to force
anything and everything you're always
forcing entries you need to take the
next setup you need to take this next
setup you need to take the next setup
you need to find another one you need to
find another and then you blame other
people for it oh what you teach doesn't
work no you don't
work that's what it is your discipline
doesn't work your ability to follow
instructions doesn't work
it's not the mentor it's
you and once you come to that
realization of that you know
just makes things a bit easier if I
follow the instructions and I follow the
rules
then I should be successful with it what
is the rules that the person that you're
learning from gave you what are the
rules if your Mentor doesn't clearly
Define rules TOS then find a new Mentor
they're just regurgitating Concepts but
can't tell you how to actually Trade It
find a new
Mentor
right or or y'all y'all just going
to slave and and Trauma bond with people
that's that's friendly to
you
[Music]
um let me see Dave in your back tested
session you said when price forms uh I I
don't have any back tested sessions
publicly so I'm not answering what I do
in the me the mentorship uh
publicly um they already got all the
leaked videos they could use
that
uh
Dave can you please reopen your
mentorship program please um I would but
I I don't want to go against my rules
usually when I do reopen it for somebody
it's usually a Karen that I'm reopening
it for and it's usually like the worst
possible person that that I could you
know reopen it for I've learned so much
with within even just the openings and
who ends up being late with it and and
most times the people who are late to
the openings are not worth even
you know having in in the group they
were late already right they didn't
prioritize it now for the people who
missed it cool but for the people didn't
prioritize it it says a lot about them
already so um yeah no I I I got to wait
until the next opening I had one guy I I
opened it late for him and he was like I
don't like the way you chastise the
members when they don't follow
instructions okay you you said you're a
40y old dad with a wife and kids and
when they don't follow instructions what
do you do what do you tell your children
but you don't want someone else
reinforcing instructions on other people
okay we'll we'll see we'll see where you
go with this I have a rental property
and no you wouldn't be searching for a
group to learn how to trade if life was
going well for you nobody cares about
your rental property have you seen the
real estate
market have you seen where all of the
savings have gone around the
country
so I'm not buying a
joker usually the the people that I I
open it for is it's just it's always a
disaster so I'm just going to wait you
know for when I do open
it um
see one thing I appreciate about you DAV
is that you call us out in our
foolishness the way you do it isn't
everyone's cup of tea but nonetheless
it's necessary and I mean most people
are not going to see it as necessary
most people need you know someone around
that's palatable
to you know their their circumstances
you ever give a friend advice and your
friend is upset that you
you gave them a solution you care so
much about them that you gave a solution
to them on how to solve whatever it is
that they claim they're dealing with and
they're angry that you gave them the
solution they want to run you around in
the circle of foolishness the circle of
oh but here's here's what I'm saying it
doesn't matter what you're saying what
matters right now is that you need to
fix the issue that's at
hand and the only way to fix the issue
that's at hand is what to deal with it
to solve it right how are you mad about
that you mad about solution driven
people in your life solution-driven
people care about
you so the first thing that they answer
is to give you a solution for it and
they're direct with you that's someone
you want to keep in your life that's
someone that actually cares about what
you're
doing you think I want to continue to
hear you getting clapped and Margin Call
and blown to smithin because you won't
even follow the instructions you were
given and I'm just going to come around
and massage
it you
know it's just the tax that we pay in
trading you didn't pay any tax that's a
tax write off you
lost you lost because you didn't follow
your rules because you didn't follow
your plan you
lost you didn't pay any taxes on
that so of course I'm going to call it
out I tell the group all the time show
me your trading plan that's the next set
the next you know segment we're going
into everybody has to show me their
trading plan and when everyone shows me
their trading plan guess what they have
to do when they start posting entries
I'm going to compare their entries with
their
plan compare the
entries with the
plan
and when I compare the entries with the
plan guess what guess guess what I'm
going to
say I'm say oh this this is
you this you here you said you said you
count your swings but the LI detect
determin you you say you you you
tregging highs and lows and and you wait
for the fourth swing but the light
detector determined that that that was
you said what you said you said when
you're in a Range you you stay out oh oh
but this entry the LI detector
determined
that and we'll go over it because you
need to stop going through this cycle of
insanity that you continue to break your
rules over and over and over
again and then you go to seek advice for
it that's Insanity how can someone give
you the answer and you go back and do
the opposite of what they
said do you actually want to train or or
you you want you want somebody to talk
to every time you break your
rules because I'll give you the therapy
hotline uh good morning Dave I kept
finding myself counting more swings than
four to six should I ignore internal
swings so you got to go back and watch
um uh video video what is that video
two because video two tells you the
internal swings and the external swings
they're from different time frames so
what time frame are you actually
counting you're not counting the one
minute swing with a a a 15 minute swing
or a one minute swing with a five minute
swing does if if you're going to get
four on the five minute how many do you
think is going to show itself on the the
one
minute so the swings are relative to the
time frames that you were trading from
so you got to make sure you you do
that
um best teachers tell you the truth
truth tellers never have friends that's
what my dad said my dad said that the
truth has no
friends he's 100%
true you ain't never lie about that the
Troth has no
friends hey Prof I know your your
uh I know you you're
weekly weekly open taret just hit I hear
that I started watching Co correct me if
I'm wrong if I want to trade on the one
minute I should watch the 15 minute
overall trend
um that that's a good start yeah but you
don't need the 15 minute you don't need
the 4 Hour you don't need any other time
frame above you other than one minute
but you need to know how it all looks
together so if you pay attention to how
it all plays out together then that's
going to help you to understand that you
could see the 15 minute in the one
minute time frame you could see the 4
Hour up move on the one minute time
frame it it doesn't matter matter what
time frame you're on you just have to
know what it's doing how it's
moving and how it looks from lower time
frame to higher time
frame so that's going to take a lot of
work that's going to take back testing
right most people hate back testing but
it's the fastest way to collect data and
I'm not talking about a data driven
dashboard that tells you whether price
is is true or false about being bullish
or bearish I'm talking about the time
you got to put in that's how you collect
the data with own
brain um what do you recommend for those
like me who picked the wrong last high
and low back testing I must be picking
them wrong because the retrace is wrong
for me that sounds like you're not back
testing what happens what do you
recommend when I keep stepping on the
the the gas instead of the
break what do you recommend what do you
recommend if if I
keep I'm supposed to drive forward and I
I hit reverse what do you recommend
that's is the this is time
right his
time I recommend you spending more time
in in you know drawing out the proper
zones dra you know trailing highs and
lows I recommend
that
time that's
needed that's what a lot of people think
time is not needed it's needed you're
not going to learn this in in in a uh
you know 10
days now you learn it in 10 days and now
you're going to become a millionaire in
the next 10
no the fastest way I've ever seen the
profitability is with profitable losers
strategy the fastest way guess what you
still got to put in the time you still
got to work for it
still you have to work for
it still got to work for
it I know I know I know trust me I know
I
know I
know why is it why is it so
difficult why do I got to why do I got
to do all of
that
why why does it take all of
that because it
does and I I didn't make the
rules it does take all of
that I I can't I can't tell you anything
different there's nothing that I can
say that will be able to change the fact
that it it it takes all of
that
right nothing that I could
say
so you got to make sure that that you're
willing to to put in the time you're
willing to do the work you got to make
sure
that no one canar
no one can my man no no one can do
it no no one can do it but
you all
right uh Dave why do I need to learn how
to walk so I can Sprint hey hey and and
that that's that's the thing that I'm
trying to get people to
understand I'm I'm really trying to get
people to understand
that you need to do it in steps it's so
important do it in
steps guys why why why did I take a
short out of here trading back into this
this uh this imbalance it more than
likely may go lower but why do I take a
short there it's probably gonna go back
in back into that uh there why don't I
take that short
there because you count your swings
right right so let's start one two 3
four five
right so now my
discretion steps up and says hey I'm not
on this side I'm on that
side I'm not going to do
this and and try to take some random
entry to go higher when I have no idea
whether another high is going to be put
in now I'm going to start to look for
moves for entries that put me in another
low and should price want to trade
higher it will trade up above this but
should price want to go lower it won't
close above this and it'll end up
Trading trading back into what previous
range
right cting my swings already it's
automatic for
me and this is just me back back to the
live
account so look yesterday I spent uh uh
yesterday I spent
uh let me show
yall yesterday I spent 20
yesterday I spent 27 minutes to make 200
bucks today I
spent one candle
into one minute
into I'm not I'm not doing free
advertisement for prop firms anymore and
I don't want to be around prop Traders
at all because they are gamblers and you
know it's equivalent to be around people
who don't have their life in control I
want to be around people who are trying
to trade and learn how to become Traders
learn how to become investors through
their understanding of how the charts
move that crowd that crazy wild crowd
I'm I'm not trying to be a part of
anymore there's there's not people that
I that I want to associate with
anymore so I'm moving away from the
whole prop scene and I'll go back to
live trading because I've done it before
that's how I became profitable trading
my own
money you said you never take shorts hey
what am I going to do take a long while
while I while I don't my rules is saying
otherwise I
can't I can't uh
uh I can't do anything about
that my if my rules are telling me
something else you know what what we got
to do we we got to follow the
rules we got to follow what the rules
say the rules say Hey
listen will you will you count your will
you count your 4 to6 SGS did you
anticipate price reversion and and then
my my time in the market right my time
in the
market my back
testing my forward
testing my process when my process says
this over that I can't go against
it it's not possible for me to I can't
go against
it so as much as I might be thinking hey
yeah let me take a a long to go
further that's not a part of my rules
when when my rules said this is is where
you stop doing
that this is where you cut it
out get rid of that who do you think you
are you think you control the
market you think the market runs on
you no it runs on
rules right
and rules that you need to
follow that's it
so if my rules put me on the short side
I'm on the short side if my rules put me
on the long side I'm on the long side
but whatever it is I will not go
anywhere without following my
rules all right
make sure you guys cover the kids yes I
don't want them
to I don't want them to to
um cover the years you need to back
test
right you need to back back test
BBB you need to back
test that's where that comes from back
testing your whole life will change the
minute you back test guys guess what
this is this is
retail this is this is retail oh my
goodness it's loud in my ears you just
they just they just ping me aggressive
you you she ain't even want to pay me
she said Target buil y y'all hear how
loud that was this is retail support and
resistance right we said it all works
right so they get the false break up
above right no body right trades back
below they get the body break and on
their body break what are they
anticipating price trading back
into what what should be
support to try and trade higher there
are times where that fails for them and
then they end up getting in on
the
breakdown and take it lower it all
occurs the same exact way it all happens
it's just
you it's just you now somebody asked me
so what zone did you that that's that's
what you should have learned in back
testing and all of that other stuff
that's what you should have learned then
we have nothing here but this large
candle that just
went some of y'all remember that some of
y'all stop losses got cooked in there
some y'all remember
that but you need the right
side you need to understand how to
engage so why did I say I was on this
side
again because my rules
for the market trending
up let me know you need to chill right
here you a you ain't got to be a part of
everything but you need to chill right
here cuz this is either what where we
range because we took out a old high so
we end up accumulating above old high so
this either where we range or this is
where we reverse
right range or reverse that's my
uh Prophet already took his
Prophet his toar already hit he just
passed the
Baton
so make sure that anything that's taught
here to you guys on this channel you go
and you back test you search it out for
yourself no one else is rebranded oh the
shorter videos are no you talking about
shorter videos the problem is you lack
discipline
you want shorter videos the only shorter
videos I recommend you to watch is
profitable losers
videos everything else is going to be
entirely
complex and if you don't have the
discipline to follow it all then you
need to be honest with yourself and say
hey
I'm that's that's not for me it's it's
difficult for me to take it all
in it's difficult for me to understand
in detail these things
occurring so I need something simpler
you don't bash the person that that has
something more complex than your brain
can
understand you go and search for things
that are
simpler told you when I was in mx's
group 30% win rate there's absolutely no
way
that I was that my kids didn't need to
eat 30% of the time they needed to eat
more than
that so why on God's green
earth would I be hanging
around a mentor who only wins 30% or I
don't care about your R get your R out
of
here I needed something that did not
exhaust my mental
capital and the market was the only
thing that taught me that nothing else
no one else the
market
market so no matter what you actually
learn out there no matter what you
actually learn out
there you need to be disciplined with
it you need to test it time and time
again back test it you can do all of
this during the during the New York
session and spend a whole eight hours
here and guess what you got you got
eight hours worth of data and that's
it eight hours worth of data today
that's going to look a little different
tomorrow and tomorrow being that it
looks a little different now you have
eight hours of data tomorrow that's
going to look a little bit different the
following
day but if you take time to back test
during that eight hours you could back
test weeks of days
in 8
hours you can you can take one
hour to back test one New York
session and soon enough you start to see
similarities by the time you get to the
sixth or seventh
hour but most people think back testing
don't work and back testing doesn't work
for people who
are you know
unprofitable back testing is not even
real
okay whatever you want to say
okay back testing is the only way for
you to get this as fast as you need to
and change your life it is the only way
the only way and then back testing helps
you to develop
rules that's the thing that most of you
guys are missing rules
so can't ask me what I was seeing and
why I thought I was taking a short and
then and then oh you took another short
then but what so you couldn't at least
let us know it no go and back
test you will never need to depend on
anybody else you think somebody needs to
be responsible for feeding my kids more
than I
do really
somebody needs needs to be responsible
for feeding my kids no me it depends on
me depends on
me so I'm taking that into my own
hands through spending time learning
what works and what
doesn't
so so the way you back test let me this
is what I do in the group when I back
toest I scroll out I go all the way back
to as far as I can I don't know where's
the furthest right
here so you see this starts at 1800 I
might want to move into you know like
some session that I I may trade you know
London's nice you know but New York if
I'm interested in trading New York I'll
move into New York like this and I'll
click it like that right so now I don't
know anything that's occurred within
here this is March 17th it's currently
April 11th I don't know anything that
occurred in here so what I do is
Click look at what we have
here and all I see is
this boy this was the Asia that they
just started
running all I see is
this so now that I have this
here what am I instantly doing
identifying where my highs and lows
are I don't know if price came from down
here I don't know if price came from up
there all I know is that I
have that high and low I have another
high and low in here I have another high
and low in there and they're relative to
the time frame that that they come from
right so in video three I mentioned how
to figure out what time frame you're
swings come
from please watch the material that's
why you're getting cooked every day
because you have no discipline to sit
down and watch that but you want to
watch the fight right you could have a
large conversation a long conversation
about who won the fight you could talk
about what pu said to Tucker you could
talk about all these different things
you can't talk about what what time
frame your swings are from and it's
literally right
there
but
digress so I have three swings
here so I'm of the understanding that if
we put in another swing here if we let's
say we go down put another swing here
another high there we got that one right
there that's the fourth one so now what
am I doing with the no noticing that
there's a fourth swing now I'm
anticipating what a potential range
right we could end up ranging shooting
back up above this and then dipping
below the range only to go back into the
range there that's from my understanding
of already knowing how price moves
you're never going to be there at least
not right
now but that's from my
understanding so if you play it
forward there's the other
swing we putting this Higher One there's
range that we talked
about and we get back in there back back
at the bottom of this range here we say
we accumulating right we go back below
this range right oh my oh my goodness
wait did did he schedule this he he had
to did he scheduled
this I can speed up and do that you
cannot you need to follow your highs and
lows and you need to take trades within
your understanding of what these highs
and lows
are
but you you're not going to you know
come to any real conclusion of
that if you don't
first understand the
material if you don't first learn the
material you need to learn the
material y'all hear me you need to learn
the
material you need to there's no if ends
or butts about
it you need to learn the
material that's the only way that that
you're going to you know find any
success than doing
this I don't care what you think about
what you actually need to utilize to
trade with and and how you just need to
see another person's entries and I don't
care about any of
that if you don't have the knowledge of
of what they're executing
on how they're
executing then you're never going to
understand why they took the entry they
took you're never going to understand
that chat when
silent Dave after the droids yeah I'm
I'm sure they they got a little surprise
on that but surprise surprise you can
learn on your own
too you can do it by yourself as
well you don't need anybody
else you don't need anyone else but
you I promise you that you don't need
anyone else but
you
so Dave have you considered packaging
your knowledge in a free
PDF or maybe a series of videos with a
catchy name maybe top class or master
plan no I haven't thought about
that those things don't really
work they they don't you know as much as
we you know love to see a PDF as much as
we th those things are not going to help
no one's going to really learn from that
there's so many PDFs out there of how to
trade ICT Concepts why nobody why nobody
know anything from
that why people still
struggling here are the fbgs you use are
you still getting cooked on
fbgs so no not not interested in it
I already screenshot the videos and
studi the concepts I don't
understand um screenshot the concepts I
don't understand and do it again so back
testing is going to be the thing that
that changes it all for
you I'm telling you nothing else but
back testing nothing else else but back
y y'all hear me nothing else but back
testing or else you willing to sit here
for the next five years and and come to
the conclusion of whatever price is
doing every single day that you come
here to trade unless you're willing to
do
that if you're willing to do that then
then hey you
know there that's fine you want to add
five years to your profitability go
ahead
how much percent you make in a month or
a day I don't follow
percentages could you go over how you
back test I just
did a PDF I just want a single picture
of all of his Concepts I literally
taught that in in the updated Market
structure plus zones and Candlestick
structure Market structure plus zones
along with candlestick structure it's
literally taught there you in the
mentorship and you asking that you got
to be
crazy literally that's a short there's
two short videos three short videos of
that and you just want something else no
you don't want to back test just say
that you don't want to back test you
don't want to be accountable to how you
spend your time you just want it quick
fast and easy right you want it Vegas
style you should not be using the
seconds time frame if you're not
profitable with the lower time
frames you should not be using the
seconds time frame if you're not
profitable with the lower time
frames you should not be using the
seconds time frame if you're not
profitable with the lower time frames
people want to use the the 5sec chart
you know and all of that you you should
you should not be down on those lower
time frames if you're not even
profitable on a one minute it makes no
sense for you to be down
there that's how to lose your account
and 10
trades people should go for what they
resonate with then when I watch video 3
I know I have found my holy Grill uh
thanks Dave don't worry you GNA be back
here asking more questions after
that he said he found the holy GRA with
one
video uh do you have any advice on
overcoming external pressures when
trading financial and emotional um
unfortunately you know my reason why was
enough for me to follow my trade plan my
reason
why that was my
kids that was me not having enough money
to buy food for
them it was me skipping meals and them
listening to the landlord knock on the
door when I didn't have money to keep
the roof over our head and I prioritized
wasting my time wasting my
life that's what I
prioritized I prioritize that cover K is
yo I prioritize
that
wasting wasting my
time and
wasting my life that that's what I was
doing and when I looked up
I realized how much I lost and how much
more they lost because what I wasn't
following a plan I wasn't following
rules I wasn't thinking about ahead
instead of right
now it's crazy
right it's
crazy so I owed it to them
to develop a set of rules that I did not
disobey because it wasn't even for me it
wasn't for the lambo it wasn't for the
Mansion it was to keep
shelter over their
heads it was to keep food on the table
it was to ensure that when they get to a
future as adults they could sustain
themselves that's what it was for
so you know that that was enough for me
to say hey Mr
teachers you you got to follow your
rules somebody else depends on
you and I know you're a big fan of doing
what you want to do but right
now this ain't the time for
it and and that changed everything it
was it was
accountability
accountability y see y they they
dropping back into back
into same stuff every day it's
you every day same stuff
it's
you it's you it's
you same stuff every
day it's
you
so I I would hope that this you
know sort of sort of shed some light on
why you guys have to have a rule ass
system a plan in place
right
oh Lou my ear
baby a
plan in place
just show y'all where I'm at with this
Live account I know I said I was going
to start Minis on on
uh I was going to start Minis on what
what day I was Monday
but this price action just been so
delicious
that the micros just couldn't
do and I'm talking to y'all while I'm
doing this I don't need to
h i don't need to to do any of that I
don't need to you know this is a trading
space so you need to be sure I'm talking
to y'all and thinking about other things
while I'm pushing the button on what I
know usually happens
right based on what I back
tested and and and what did we say we we
said we said we said I Concepts do work
too as well right right so what is
that man said run the low rebalance to
an
F that that's this I'm telling you I'm G
find his name because it was like just
such a simple thing that that he he
talked about and I'm like wait a minute
you mean to tell me all these guys on
Twitter are frauds wait a
minute
okay yeah
sure do what you got to do
okay I'm going just take my little
trades when I take them and and then
exit the market and guess what they said
they said you can't do that in the S
environment okay okay buddy you can't do
that in the Sim fight
okay it's it's abusing simp because in a
real environment this is what we
okay okay
man HD is not bad forly time forite yeah
that that's true that's true anything
anything everything more than 600 people
and 200 like that's fine they don't like
they don't got to like the video I like
me I like me for both of us so they
didn't even have to like
it I like me more than they like me
so you don't have to you know
thanks I'm profitable when back testing
can pass evals but when I get to funded
I crumble that's because you stop doing
the things that you did during back
testing and
evals back testing the evals is no
different than a live
account if I would take this trade in
back testing the evals I would take this
trade in Live account if I would count
my swings in back testing an evils I'm
would count my swings when I'm taking a
live trade there's no
difference the only difference for that
matter is
you the market does the same thing in
Market replay and it does the same thing
with you on
evals
[Music]
so you you picking up what I'm putting
down
it's you you got to take the same hey
Prof always
say the move is more valuable than the
money and that's 100%
true the
move it's far more
valuable than the
money the
move is more
valuable than the he ain't never
lie he said the move is more valuable
y'all y'all listening to
me or y'all tuning me
out the
move more valuable than the
money and that's
100 10%
true trade the move not the
money don't worry the money will show
up after you've mastered the move the
money will show
up after you mastered the the money will
show up after you mastered the
move but some of y'all trading all these
different things and and
you all got the V app on your chart you
get the bowling your bands and and they
both saying different things they
arguing with each
other the V app say we going
bearish the non EMA saying no no fam we
bullish the Binger band saying I don't
know what y'all talking about I'm here
in the
middle the Marg structure saying I'm
coming for your stop loss
all these different things being said
and you don't know which one to follow
because you have not mastered the
move he said vshape recovery coming I I
don't know but
that let's let us
see yeah I can I can test to
that the market gonna have to show
me what it's doing I can't tell it what
it's doing it tells
me
yeah it it it tells me I I can't
say what I think it's
doing
our entries suck back test that that's
what I tell people back testing tells
you that your entries are
garbage that's what back testin
does see a little Wick up above this
high as well so we Wick below this low
Wick up above this High we'll see if you
get a body closure up there it could
move higher into here but if that Wick
stays there then you probably end up
crumbling back below
this but that that's what back testing
tells you back Tes tells you hey hey fam
listen those entries that you think you
you know you you think you
think don't those entries
suck there back to those
entries they
suck that's what back tting
say
o
so if you guys if you guys actually
watch the Youtube I know I know I know I
know it's it's the videos are too long
they too long so we we can't come
on they too long how you supposed to
make
money in that they they too
long did say one to on pay the
bill right there
right through
there
right
so what you think I put this low here
this this thing here right below that
low
y that bad boy be having in so
fast
man one to one's pay the
bill I don't know why people be forcing
anything
different I get it I get it you know
y'all want the 100 point you know like
you you want you want this right you
want you want this you you want to trade
the news event you know and be like yeah
it it hit the 50% and then I held it all
the way up and then and then all the way
up from from there and then yeah I got
the 100 Point move you you want you want
you you want that
right in the most liquid Market one of
the most liquid markets in the world you
you worry you worri about
that you
wor you you wor
about and one of the most liquid boes in
the world you
yes let let me let me just get us let
get some music they they they need some
music they need some
music they wor about
that we they we did three and a half
pennies they worry about that okay they
a take no money on the market all yeah
anyway
yo
[Music]
you you bring the love that I
need you bring
the you bring the love that I need
feeling so real
you you bring the love that I need you
bring the he feeling it's so real you
bring the he you bring the love that I
need you
bring feeling so
[Music]
real you bring the love that
I you bring the
you bring the love that I need feeling
so real you
bring you bring the
I
[Music]
youing my man said you talk as you were
gone okay I I talk like I know myself
and I'm
disciplined I talk like I'm
disciplined
there I talk like I possess a certain
level of discipline and most people
don't you bring the love that I need you
bring feeling
you bring the you bring the love that I
you bring the feeling so real you bring
the you bring the love that I you bring
the feeling so real you bring the he you
bring the love that I you bring the he
feeling so
[Music]
real
you you the
I
you you bring the love that I feeling
you
youing you bring the love that I
you you the that I feel
[Music]
real you the that
I
you you the that I feel
next
hey he
so uh yeah I I don't know why people
come on the stream just to
like waste their
time what what is second any of this
doing to
me y'all see how I still trade with the
trolls around still trade
[Laughter]
with so how you deal with the external
external what I back test so much that I
remember this more than my own
name I remember this more than I got to
think twice about my mother's
number but I know 30 I know 50 and
I
what back there just like my life
depended on it what do you
[Music]
think great day in the morning
why I got you Elijah I got you here you
go here you go this for Elijah he asked
hey the storm is over you made it stop
i' come to find you're what I want so I
laugh about it my tears are dry don't
doubt about it I'll be all right my pass
behind me I'm Let It Go and all that I
know it's going to be
better it's going to be
better it's s Sweet
can it's going to be
better it's going to be
[Music]
better going to be
better
[Music]
found
found Hey listen I'm telling you all all
the concepts work this y'all look we
take out that high right where do we
go
rebalance through an FG Dre High come on
Jamon it it
all it
all it's going to be
better it's going to be
better it's song is with
together it's going to be better
it's going to be better now all
found
found I'm
not
[Music]
found it's going to
be
as long as we're
together it's going to be
better it's going to be
[Music]
[Applause]
better it's going to be better
now oh long as we
together all right all right all right
so
uh somebody said
uh uh where is it um can you explain
quickly what do you mean by memory so
this is just the stuff that I remember
in back
testing was literally
that nothing different I just remember
all of this when I was back
testing so what I'm teaching is or and
what I'm trading is based on what I
remember price to
do that's why no PDF is ever going to
help you no short video of nothing is
ever going to help
you none of it at all it will never help
you you have to go through it yourself
you have to put in the time
yourself and that's the only thing
that's that's really going to you know
change the the way that you
trade
so what I'm teaching is from my memory
of a culmination of things that I've
learned and found it works if you do it
like
this if you do it this way it works so
if you actually want to follow me you
got to follow the the teachings that's
there it works
works but all of these same things other
people
teach ICT uses
imbalances some of people use supply and
demand some people don't some people use
Elliot wav some people
don't but whatever it is that I use I
use it in a way where it works for me
and I teach based on what works for me
so guess what if it works for me it
should work for you too if you apply it
the same
way if you apply it the same exact way
that I teach
it it should work for
you because it works for me I'm not
teaching something that somebody else
taught and told me it does
this told me that it does this no I've
made hundreds of thousands of dollars
using this
alone I know it
works it works so good that people
accuse me of stealing it from other
people so why those people not using it
the same way why they not why do we rate
so
low why they W sit here in a live market
and just Peace by piece by piece go
through the whole thing with you why you
not doing
that
that's why I'm able to stand up in front
of y'all and and you talk the way I
do course say little B you talk a lot do
the tra baby who of course I'mma do all
that I know it
works you need to be
humble y the market already humbled me
okay it CLA me
already the market it it stole my WI it
it like everything was gone everything
it took it all it took it all from
me he said it could we could have had it
on it took it all from
me the market robbed me he said you
think you know what you doing millions
of people coming to this market and you
you think
you
you target filled than you what you
doing you the mark the marketer R did
all that to
me came out refined on the other
side
you Paul I know Peter I
know who are
you Mark put me
on
it put me
[Music]
on
do
treat smile you can't have what's next
till you hang with it for a while this
is house arrest
come but we your Sunday
Best this is house
[Music]
arrestar me I was I you sleep do
you sadness with a smile you have next
you it for a while this is how
come to we you're Sunday
F this is
house this is
[Music]
house this is house AR
rest come to wear your Sunday
F this is
[Music]
house
I decided not to leave my house and go
outside I help myself sweet made
[Music]
myself so
uh this is
uh m
[Music]
M this target
build this is
how
[Music]
this is house
arrest
beautiful
beautiful so uh it is the same stuff
over and over right and over and over
right and over and over right and over
and over right and over and over why why
did I take that
long well there's a previous range right
that it tapped into
right hit the 50% tra to the one to one
on it right right right we we all we all
follow that
man that was
taunt and guess what that's all
free it's all
free
free f
r
e
free that's all freely
taught in the master class playlist
right
so you know when when we uh
uh maybe another balance in
301 when we uh
uh see people coming in talking about
scammer this scammer that you
know you all the complaining they
do you you know that is you know where
that's coming
from
they they don't know what they talking
about and it's all free for
them it's there and it's
free is there and it's
free is there and is
free
it's there and it's
free it's
de hey you know let me let me let me
turn on turn on
another
banger
[Music]
are so we can be free strange things
happen here it's the time to leave if we
being met at midnight at theow tree are
you are you coming here with me to run
by so we can be free strange things
happen here it's the time to leave if
we tree are you are
you to my side so we can be free strange
things to happen here it's the time to
leave if we met at midnight theow tree
are you are you coming here with me to
run by side so we can be free strange
things do happen here it's the time to
leave
midnight Target fell
you and me to run by my side so we can
be free strange things to happen here
it's the time to if
we to
by strange things
this time
[Music]
to are you are you come here with me to
run by my side so we can be free strange
things to happen
time we
midnight
[Music]
I I told y'all 301 that's what I say
right are you coming here with me to R
by my side so we can free strange things
happen here it's the time to leave if we
met midnight the
Tre we be free strange things here it's
to
midnight
[Music]
tree
now y'all I'm not going to act like I
know where this volatility is coming
from I
don't
but we don't
care because it's the same stuff that
you see
over and
over and over and they they tell me what
time time it is did I ask y'all what
time it
was I don't think I I
[Music]
don't r on my
side things things to
happen
so
yes we
don't you know subscribe
to any of that stuff because we know
what we know what we're
doing we know know you know what we
could anticipate we know like at at
least myself you know you got some
students who are streaming and you guys
need to understand that they're learning
themselves too so you have to take what
they're saying with a grain of salt
because they're learning to develop
themselves and they're doing it for the
sake of
accountability right they're doing it
for the sake of
accountability so if they're doing it to
hold themselves accountable to not take
dumb entries it's easier for for people
to hold themselves accountable in
trading when somebody's watching them
versus when somebody's not watching them
so that's why they're doing it it's not
to say that they're ready to teach
anybody
anything but it's for them to bring you
know that recklessness under control and
trade like people are paying attention
to the the things that they're
doing but I told you all that I said 3
301 what was that 301 something like
that yeah
301 it's another Bounce from
there yeah and you just watch this you
know I know some somebody's like cuz I I
took it up here but somebody's like you
know of course of course uh why did you
just take the whole thing that you know
like like I said the most liquid Market
in the world and y'all and y'all worryed
yall
worried y'all yall worried about 100
Point moves and and all of that you know
it it's not me guy it's not
me this I can trade whatever I want I
could trade enq I could trade gold I
could trade you whatever these other
things are here you know um oil I'm
probably going to get into that you know
in a feud throughout Asia and stuff like
that trade whatever it is I
want and do it the same way I would do
it on Prom do the same way I've done it
on unregulated Brokers same exact thing
each and every time it doesn't matter we
trade above a whole High what do we know
we accumulate we know that when we
accumulate long as the bottom of the
range short at the top of the
range until we get a range failure and
then price trades what back into the
range and should price want to go higher
it trade up above the range but if it
doesn't it'll trade below and keep going
down it's the same stuff each and every
day I've done this with the U the the
member subscriptions on YouTube I
explained this little phenomenon to you
guys you know again this this is you see
how you see us
pushing I don't think price is going to
get a lick of buy
side this is not going back
up this is not this is why you don't
follow anybody on
Twitter this is not going back
up not going to get a l b
sign okay
buddy this The Dark Knight trade when
you going to say his name
here
but this this this is the reality of it
you don't need news you don't need need
to figure out what time it is no nothing
like that you see that entry was a news
entry anybody get about that prop Fern's
telling people don't trade news hor the
the fils during new I'm telling that
that just filled me and took me
out
that they fill me and took me
out like that in a
rush so
um you see you you
uh you know
you you follow your rules you follow
your plan you trade with what you know
you see not what you think I didn't want
I didn't think oh I'm I'm thinking price
is going to go back into this previous
range here who told you
that where where do they where do they
do that
at who told you that that it had to go
back
in who told you that you caught the top
up
here
yeah we caught the top going
down and and
still cooking
you stop loss is
searing right
now you lay me y up
there
so you just got to know what you're
doing you got to be honest with your
your uh
uh your
approach you you got to be
honest with it you got to be honest with
your
experience you got to be honest with
that um
I was out bro did you mention your real
Instagram um it's Dave teachers that's
it nothing else I'm the only Dave
teachers nothing before it nothing after
it but you got to be honest with your
experience and if you're honest with
your experience then your your prophets
will be honest with
you they tell you good
job if you dishonest your Prophet to
tell you you never make this you could
never do this Mar see the whole thing
happening all over the place right what
do we say about
retail we are retail too but what do we
say we said that they get the break
above they
retest the resistance now turn support
and they look to trade higher you don't
see them
there I know over here over here they
they really they really didn't get the
best the best kind of I mean yeah it's
breaking retest there too and trade
higher that that happened for them there
too but they don't always get the best
you know thing look down below here
that's that's the break below this right
with the body it retest and then went
right back up and traded back to to the
high they they get cooked sometimes but
you know what I know I know they make
more money than the people who prounce
around Twitter trying to tell people
that they're wrong for what they're
doing I knew something was off with him
because he said he doesn't use time you
hear no mention of daily
bias you you hear no
man you hear no
mention
I'm like boy these people so guys look
I'm leave youall with this it's time for
you guys to go back to time for you guys
to hang up trying to trade live and go
find that one thing that you good at in
back
testing find that one
thing that you are good at in back that
one thing just find that one thing you
are good at in back
testing and that you know within it self
should you change everything for
you you find out one thing you find out
one thing and you be
sent because you don't need to trade
everything you don't need to see all
happening you don't even need to be
right about it you just need to know how
to approach the market with that one
thing that you know you see all the time
an exit on your
experience take your profit live to see
the next
day so
um I appreciate you guys for for coming
out I know
I'm I'm a
handful at times and that's
okay but
um you know have some have some pride in
in your your work your work ethic you're
study and have some pride in it I'm
telling you the people who do not make
it when learning these concepts are the
people who take no notes I know it feels
like high school all over again you hate
you know doing notes and you know all
that other good jazz do it take your
notes take your
notes take your notes take it take your
notes that muscle memory will go a lot
further than you believe have some
pride have some PR pride in the work
that you do
right have some pride in the work that
you
do because you're not doing this for you
you're doing this for your reason why
there are people who depend on
you act like
it so I'm leave youall with this
banger
he
[Music]
be
this
so y'all that's that's this 200 today
1100 I mean 200 yesterday 1100
today if I wanted to I could withdraw
that
today and start all over again tomorrow
right
that's the beauty of trading for
yourself made a th a day now I don't
have to have
5,000 in my account before I withdraw
don't have to have a 10day limit of
whatever it is that I don't think y'all
hear
me I don't think y'all hear
[Music]
me
i
[Music]
up
so there there's no limits as far as I'm
concern there's no limits to your
accounts I'm going to start copy trading
the Live account soon so I'm going to
try to have like four or five of them
and then copy trade each of them to
spread the risk across each other and
that way you don't have to use a large
contra track size on one position you
would spread the risk across multiple
accounts and now you're just copy
trading
yourself and then you just pay yourself
at the end of each day
right
all right y'all so I hope you guys enjoy
this stream the first half of the stream
I'm going try to cut that video and then
place it into the the playlist as like a
you know I don't know accountability
video something like that um the first
playlist um the original one that has 12
videos in it because it's a 12-step
program y'all know for those Alcoholic
Anonymous all that other stuff that you
see y'all know that there there uh uh
you know that kind of stuff is a 12-step
program to get over that right so the
name of the group is ched anonymous
because you know we we are addicted to
the chase of trading to make money right
I I know that I'm I'm on charts more
than I talk to friends what friends I
don't even have friends so you know for
me I know that I'm addicted to being
right right I'm
addicted let me stop I'm addicted to to
you know trading I know that so there
fashioned around that it's for people
who are addicts for a better future at
least the everybody's addicted to
something at least it's a positive
addiction you got the 12-step program
that brings you in right cleans you up
clean out all of that stuff that's in
your your gut you clean all that stuff
up hey and if you choose to join you
join if you don't choose to join you
don't have to join people that ain't
never been in the mentorship killing it
right now you don't ever have to
join never you you ain't never got to
pay me a dime you can do the same stuff
I'm doing free f for
re you don't ever have to
join that's for people who want actual
mentorship and I don't care whether you
like the way I talk to you or not if you
keep breaking your rules of course the
market is going to break you so at least
I'm there to save some of
it at least I'm there to to talk you
through the realness of it right cuz if
you keep running in this circle chasing
your tail at some point you're going to
look up
and boy you ain't going to recognize the
life that that you thought you were
creating you thought you were
chasing so many people lost their
Partners over this lost their families
over this
and they look up with nothing never
gained profitability but they lost
everything for
it and I'm trying to stop you from
from you know incurring those
losses just if you willing to listen or
not so we going to tell you hey stop
chasing your tail you're wrong with
doing this why won't you watch it
properly and take notes yeah somebody
needs to be behind you like that because
you can't be trusted yourself to follow
it the way you need to so of course
somebody has to be there and if I'm
responsible for the development of you
as a
traiter if I'm responsible for
that then I'm going to be very
passionate about it I'm going to treat
it as if I'm teaching my own cuz guess
what my own rejected
this my
own rejected this
I learned this for them and they didn't
even want to be a part of
it so of course I'm teaching you like
it's like it's my brother like it's my
sister like it's my mother like whoever
it is I'm going to teach you what you
need to know so you don't need me but if
you choose to continue doing the things
you are doing you're going to need alone
you're going to you're going to need a
doctor and you're going need a job if
you keep running in that same Circle
right so uh I catch up with y'all soon
appreciate y'all for coming out later
y tell your mother stop
yelling